我敢打赌，一旦我停止讲话，海ry就会打开，好吧，让我们尝试一下
I bet the dory will open as soon as I stop talking okay let's try it
stop talking okay let's try it so 1231 okay you can you count the
所以1231好吧，您可以算一下门打开的秒数，因此
so 1231 okay you can you count the seconds when the door will open so the
seconds when the door will open so the main topic today is what is called the
今天的主要主题是所谓的消除算法
main topic today is what is called the elimination algorithm that sort of we
elimination algorithm that sort of we have sort of seen it with examples up to
到目前为止，我们已经通过示例看到了它，但我们将尝试在一个示例中做到这一点。
have sort of seen it with examples up to now but we're going to try to do it in a
now but we're going to try to do it in a sort of graph theoretic manner but
某种图论的方式，但在此之前，我需要介绍一下，如果您
sort of graph theoretic manner but before that I need to cover maybe if you
before that I need to cover maybe if you slice from the previous lecture if you
如果您还记得我们在讲的话，请看上一讲的片段，看看我
slice from the previous lecture if you remember we're talking about you see I
remember we're talking about you see I was right
没关系，所以我们要说的不是
was right okay so we are going to talk it was not
okay so we are going to talk it was not about you okay so we're going to talk
关于你好吧，所以我们将讨论其中一些例子
about you okay so we're going to talk about examples of actually some of them
about examples of actually some of them we will see in very fine detail so it
我们将看到非常详细的信息，因此稍后再说，在
we will see in very fine detail so it later on said things look weird in the
later on said things look weird in the context of Bayesian inference for gosh
贝叶斯推论的上下文我们还没有看到这些东西，我们将
context of Bayesian inference for gosh we have not seen these things we will
we have not seen these things we will come back to those things later on so
稍后再回到这些事情，所以我们已经做过的例子就是一个
come back to those things later on so the example that we already did was one
the example that we already did was one of polynomial regression so this
多项式回归，所以实际上这只是贝叶斯线性回归
of polynomial regression so this actually just Bayesian linear regression
actually just Bayesian linear regression so we treat the response of the system
所以我们对待标量系统的响应，我们称其为P
so we treat the response of the system which is scalar and we call it P to some
which is scalar and we call it P to some polynomial with this coefficients WI
系数WI是随机变量的多项式，我们写了
polynomial with this coefficients WI being random variables and we wrote the
being random variables and we wrote the joint probability distribution like that
这样的联合概率分布，所以这是W的先验，这是
joint probability distribution like that so this is the prior of W and this is
so this is the prior of W and this is the likelihood so if when you W with the
的可能性，所以如果当你W的概率在这里还可以，而这是在
the likelihood so if when you W with the probability of here okay and this is in
probability of here okay and this is in its most general form all right where W
它最一般的形式好吧，W在Davi上具有先验，其高度为
its most general form all right where W has the prior on Davi has some height of
has the prior on Davi has some height of our meters alpha and this likelihood
我们的米alpha和它的W输入的似然模型取决于
our meters alpha and this likelihood model for its input for its W depends on
model for its input for its W depends on some noise variance Sigma square which
一些未知的方差Sigma平方，所以这又是
some noise variance Sigma square which is not known so this is sort of again in
is not known so this is sort of again in more detail the joint probability of T
更详细地说明了T的联合概率，即未知的响应和W
more detail the joint probability of T these the response and W of the unknown
these the response and W of the unknown regression coefficients so what we did
回归系数，所以我们做了这个介绍，我们引入了这种平板符号
regression coefficients so what we did this we introduced this plate notation
this we introduced this plate notation and the everything is inside the box
而且所有东西都在盒子里面，这意味着它要重复n次，所以当
and the everything is inside the box means it is repeating n times so when
means it is repeating n times so when you say you see here you know when you
你说你看到这里，你知道当你尝试写联合概率时
you say you see here you know when you try to write the joint probability
try to write the joint probability distribution of all the variables on
该模型上所有变量的分布，您将拥有
distribution of all the variables on this model you're going to have the
this model you're going to have the probability of TN given X 10 but now you
给定TN的概率为X 10，但现在有n个，这就是您得到的方式
probability of TN given X 10 but now you have n of those and that's how you get
have n of those and that's how you get this product and of course you have the
该乘积，当然您有W给出alpha和alpha的概率
this product and of course you have the probability of W given alpha and alpha
probability of W given alpha and alpha and Sigma square is taken as fixed
而西格玛平方现在被当作固定参数，所以没有
and Sigma square is taken as fixed parameters right now so there's no
parameters right now so there's no probability affiliated to them so this
属于它们的概率，所以这是车牌符号，当您获得
probability affiliated to them so this is the plate notation and when you get
is the plate notation and when you get expert in this type of things sometimes
这类事情的专家有时您会在这本书上画这个像素
expert in this type of things sometimes you will be drawing this book this pixel
you will be drawing this book this pixel sphere and immediately implying this a
领域，并立即暗示了许多其他内容
sphere and immediately implying this a lot of other writing this and that
lot of other writing this and that saying here is the picture showing the
说这里是显示分布还可以的图片，但是需要一些时间
saying here is the picture showing the distribution okay but it will take some
distribution okay but it will take some time basically to get rain on doing that
基本上可以花些时间去做，但是在很多论文中人们都没有
time basically to get rain on doing that but in a lots of papers people don't
but in a lots of papers people don't want to do to solve the answer bus or
想做解决答案总线或他们看到的是这个，这意味着
want to do to solve the answer bus or what they saw is this and that implies
what they saw is this and that implies everything you need to know okay and I
您需要知道的所有信息，我想我们首先要扩展它
everything you need to know okay and I think we want to extend it first you
think we want to extend it first you know in the last few seconds of the
在上周四的演讲的最后几秒钟内知道
know in the last few seconds of the presentation last Thursday to include
presentation last Thursday to include also predictions so this is the joint
也是预测，所以这是W的联合概率分布
also predictions so this is the joint probability distribution of W of the
probability distribution of W of the training data the build is the training
训练数据的构建是对应于X球的训练数据，而且我们
training data the build is the training data corresponding to X ball and also we
data corresponding to X ball and also we have the prediction stick heart
拥有对应于X 1/2的预测棒心，因此，如果您尝试
have the prediction stick heart corresponding to X 1/2 so if you try to
corresponding to X 1/2 so if you try to form this joint distribution basically
基本上形成这种联合分布，这就是后验
form this joint distribution basically what you have is this is the posterior
what you have is this is the posterior of W this is what we had before but also
W这是我们以前拥有的，但现在您也看到了轻液体
of W this is what we had before but also now you see the light liquid
now you see the light liquid corresponding to X hot okay so this is
对应于X hot好的，所以这是给定X帽子的大心脏的概率
corresponding to X hot okay so this is the probability of big heart given X hat
the probability of big heart given X hat and given the parameters W Sigma square
并给定参数W Sigma平方，再次如图所示，我们具有相同的
and given the parameters W Sigma square and again pictorially we have the same
and again pictorially we have the same thing as before but not what we have
和以前一样，但我们没有做的是，我们已经包含了一个说明，
thing as before but not what we have done is we have included a note that
done is we have included a note that will allow us for any text heart to
将使我们对任何文本的心都可以算出预测的大心
will allow us for any text heart to figure out what the prediction big heart
figure out what the prediction big heart is and you notice this prediction the
是，您会注意到这种预测，心脏取决于下一个心脏
is and you notice this prediction the heart depends for next heart it depends
heart depends for next heart it depends from w and it depends on Sigma square so
从w开始，它取决于Sigma平方，所以箭头基本上是指向所有
from w and it depends on Sigma square so the arrows basically is to all the
the arrows basically is to all the dependencies that you need to know so
您需要了解的过于极端的依赖关系很复杂，但是
dependencies that you need to know so too extreme is complicated right but on
too extreme is complicated right but on the other hand someone would say this is
另一方面，有人会说这已经很复杂了
the other hand someone would say this is complicated already well this
complicated already well this incorporates the full model again if you
如果您没有在模型中看到此问题，请再次合并完整模型
incorporates the full model again if you have not seen this problems in the
have not seen this problems in the context of regression it will take you
回归的背景，您花不到20分钟的时间阅读我的
context of regression it will take you less than 20 minutes to read my
less than 20 minutes to read my regression lecture from not semester or
不上学期的回归讲座，或者像主教一样看书或
regression lecture from not semester or looking at the book like bishops or
looking at the book like bishops or leftist view to get some idea on this
左派观点可以对这类事情有所了解
leftist view to get some idea on this type of thing
这是名称相关向量所伴随的另一个进展问题
that's another progression problem that goes with the name relevance vector
goes with the name relevance vector machines we actually don't believe we
我们实际上不相信我们即使在最后的课程中也无法涵盖
machines we actually don't believe we cover this even in the course last
cover this even in the course last semester but basically a simple idea you
一个学期，但基本上是一个简单的主意，它在很多方面都与
semester but basically a simple idea you it's similar in many ways to the
it's similar in many ways to the previous model but you notice now there
以前的模型，但您现在注意到边界使用周围还有另一个板块
previous model but you notice now there is another plate around the boundary use
is another plate around the boundary use and this hyper parameters alpha they're
而这些超参数alpha则位于该板中，这意味着必须
and this hyper parameters alpha they're inside this plate which means there must
inside this plate which means there must be some you that looks like that all
是一些看起来像这样的人，所以这个重复，所以我们有M
be some you that looks like that all right so this repetition so we have M
right so this repetition so we have M doubly use all right so when you look at
加倍使用，所以当您看这张照片时
doubly use all right so when you look at this picture
this picture obviously it implies for each of this W
显然，这意味着对于每只W眼，我都将自己的先验和
obviously it implies for each of this W eyes I am putting its own prior and
eyes I am putting its own prior and effectively they have the same type of
实际上，它们具有与高斯人相同的分布类型，但是
effectively they have the same type of distributions it's a gaussians but the
distributions it's a gaussians but the variance is different and the idea of
方差是不同的，这些相关的摔跤机的想法是
variance is different and the idea of these relevant wrestler machines that is
these relevant wrestler machines that is not coming this picture is that somehow
这张图片没来的是，当某些补给品
not coming this picture is that somehow when some of the supplies go to
when some of the supplies go to Trinity this distribution picks on zero
三位一体，这个分布选择零，基本上这个W变成
Trinity this distribution picks on zero and basically this W to become
and basically this W to become irrelevant in the whole picture so this
与整个图片无关，所以这就是所谓的相关向量
irrelevant in the whole picture so this is what this called relevance vector
is what this called relevance vector must change to tells you from all the
必须更改为从所有输入变量中告诉您需要哪些输入变量
must change to tells you from all the input variables which ones are needed to
input variables which ones are needed to do predictions so similar to what we had
做的预测与我们之前的预测非常相似
do predictions so similar to what we had before
before all right again this is the noise
再次好，这是模型中的噪声方差，这是您的Sigma
all right again this is the noise variance in the model this is your Sigma
variance in the model this is your Sigma squared
平方，但现在W是另一个板
squared but now the W is another plate that
but now the W is another plate that comes outside to introduce this sparsity
外来介绍这种稀疏性诱导W的先验模型，因此该移动设备
comes outside to introduce this sparsity inducing prior model of W so this mobile
inducing prior model of W so this mobile is sort of very simple but very powerful
是一种非常简单但功能强大的工具，可让您对其进行实际编程
is sort of very simple but very powerful and allows you to program it actually
and allows you to program it actually literally in the five lines so it's a a
从字面上的五行来看，如果您要测试它是一个非常喜欢的模型
literally in the five lines so it's a a very favorite model if you want to test
very favorite model if you want to test sparsity and do regression this is the
稀疏并进行回归这是您想要做的事情的类型
sparsity and do regression this is the type of things you want to do
从本质上讲，所以基本上我们只是您知道我们说让我们来做这个
on the mean well so basically we just the you know we say let's take this
the you know we say let's take this cigars and write this Gaussian it's
雪茄，并写下这个高斯，它将以零零为中心
cigars and write this Gaussian it's going to be centered around zero zero
going to be centered around zero zero means the battery is not important okay
表示电池并不重要，并且充满信心
means the battery is not important okay and and with some with some confidence
and and with some with some confidence basically defined by this precision of
基本上是由高精确度的精度定义的，所以您不知道是什么意思
basically defined by this precision of high okay so nothing you know okay
再次，该板符号不显示分布的类型是
and again this plate notation does not show the type of distributions are so
show the type of distributions are so you know if you want from Gaussian to go
你知道你是否想从高斯去其他没有学生的T分布
you know if you want from Gaussian to go to other no student T distribution
to other no student T distribution something like that at this point you
在这一点上，您也可以这样做，所以这仍然是
something like that at this point you can do that as well so this is still a
can do that as well so this is still a bit more generic okay so that's the
通用一点好吧，这就是我们要讨论的板旋转
bit more generic okay so that's the plate rotate we are going to discuss
plate rotate we are going to discuss we're going to spend maybe a whole week
我们将在隐马尔可夫模型和状态空间上花费整整一周的时间
we're going to spend maybe a whole week on hidden Markov models and state-space
on hidden Markov models and state-space models so you're going to see these
模型，所以您将多次看到这些东西，让我
models so you're going to see these things multiple times okay and let me
things multiple times okay and let me I'm gonna play pass this unsupervised
我将以这个名字的名义通过这个无人监督的学习问题
I'm gonna play pass this unsupervised learning problem under the name of
learning problem under the name of Pittsburgh component analysis maybe we
匹兹堡成分分析，也许我们将在稍后的演讲中介绍
Pittsburgh component analysis maybe we will cover this in a lecture of later on
will cover this in a lecture of later on using you know block of representation
用你知道的代表块，但我们专注于一个非常隐蔽的
using you know block of representation but then we concentrate on a very hidden
but then we concentrate on a very hidden Markov model called basically all the
马尔可夫模型称基本上所有变量都是离散的或处于状态空间
Markov model called basically all the variables are discrete or in state-space
variables are discrete or in state-space models which basically they're similar
基本上与隐马尔可夫模型相似的模型，但该轴
models which basically they're similar to hidden Markov models but this axis
to hidden Markov models but this axis are continuous variables and the
是连续变量，并且观测值Y也是连续的
are continuous variables and the observations Y are also continuous
observations Y are also continuous variables and what I have done here just
变量以及我在这里所做的事情，以便可以使外观看起来像
variables and what I have done here just so I can sort of make things to look a
so I can sort of make things to look a little complicated are not simply
有点复杂的不是简单地将这个隐藏的马尔可夫模型扩展到一个
little complicated are not simply extending this hidden Markov model to a
extending this hidden Markov model to a state space model but I'm explaining it
状态空间模型，但我正在向所谓的“到达安全空间”进行解释
state space model but I'm explaining it to what is called as reaching safe space
to what is called as reaching safe space water
水，我再说一次我在说你的地方
water and again I'm talking where I said you
and again I'm talking where I said you know of the course but you know I want
知道这门课程，但你知道我想让你看到这个东西，而且如此
know of the course but you know I want you to see this thing and Beyond so
you to see this thing and Beyond so actively this axis is the human state
积极地，这条轴是类似于您所拥有的人类状态的原因
actively this axis is the human state similar to what you have there why are
similar to what you have there why are the observations and that's the sort of
观察结果，这就是一种描述性变量，可以告诉您是否
the observations and that's the sort of a descriptive variable that tells you if
a descriptive variable that tells you if you think of this representing let's say
您认为这代表着，假设您知道一些模型和
you think of this representing let's say you know some mixture of models and the
you know some mixture of models and the state let's say s 1 can be 1 2 or 3 in
假设s 1可以是1 2或3 in
state let's say s 1 can be 1 2 or 3 in so you can be into the different
so you can be into the different components on the mixture
因此，该离散变量S 1定义了混合物中的组分
components on the mixture so this discrete variable S 1 defines
so this discrete variable S 1 defines basically import the evolution of the
基本上将动力学系统的演变从x1导入到
basically import the evolution of the dynamical system how you go from x1 to
dynamical system how you go from x1 to x2 but also defines the observation how
x2，但也定义了观察值，您如何从X到R ok获得y1，在这里
x2 but also defines the observation how you get y1 from X to R ok and here this
you get y1 from X to R ok and here this discrete particle s also evolves the
离散粒子s的演化方式也与我们在隐马尔可夫模型中的演化方式相同
discrete particle s also evolves the same way as we do in a hidden Markov
same way as we do in a hidden Markov model and the human-machine the tempest
模型和人机狂暴法则迫使第一支箭这样
model and the human-machine the tempest law sort of forcing the first arrow so
law sort of forcing the first arrow so for example if this is in the robotics
例如，如果这是在机器人中，您可能会知道一些电源输入
for example if this is in the robotics you know maybe would be some power input
you know maybe would be some power input or some force input torque or something
或一些力输入扭矩或您在模型中输入的类似内容
or some force input torque or something like that that you put in the model so
like that that you put in the model so this is the generic thing and this is
这是通用的东西，这是无限的扩展之一
this is the generic thing and this is one of the extensions there are infinite
one of the extensions there are infinite books for extensions like that and the
像这样的扩展书籍，对于那些人来说，好消息是坏消息
books for extensions like that and the good news are for the bad news for those
good news are for the bad news for those doing a PhD is that all of the smallest
做博士学位是所有最小的问题都已经解决了20年了
doing a PhD is that all of the smallest basically have been addressed 20 years
basically have been addressed 20 years ago ok so they may look complicated but
以前好，所以它们可能看起来很复杂，但是它们都完成了交易，实际上
ago ok so they may look complicated but they are all done deals and actually
they are all done deals and actually they have revolutionized areas from
他们已经彻底改变了从机器人技术到动画的领域，仅此而已
they have revolutionized areas from robotics to animation to just mention it
robotics to animation to just mention it navigation satellite tracking and all of
导航卫星跟踪以及所有这些东西
navigation satellite tracking and all of these things
these things right from but I'm giving you this is an
从现在开始，但我再次给您一个例子，您现在在这里看到的是
right from but I'm giving you this is an example again now what you see here
example again now what you see here we're going to spend more than a week or
我们将在课程中花一两个星期以上的时间，所以我
we're going to spend more than a week or two later on in the course so what I
two later on in the course so what I wanted to do is say I just wanted to
想要做的就是说我只是想向您展示仪表中的电表是如何来的
wanted to do is say I just wanted to show you how meters come in this models
show you how meters come in this models again as a background so what i'm doing
再次作为背景，所以我在这里要做的是写联合
again as a background so what i'm doing here is i'm writing the joint
here is i'm writing the joint probability of x and y in the state
x和y在状态空间模型中的概率明确表示为节点X
probability of x and y in the state space model explicitly so this is node X
space model explicitly so this is node X 1 so you started with P of X 1 and then
1，所以从X的P 1开始，然后给定X 1的y 1的P，然后给定X 2的P
1 so you started with P of X 1 and then P of y 1 given X 1 then P of X 2 given
P of y 1 given X 1 then P of X 2 given x1 and then give right to given X 2 etc
x1然后赋予给定的X 2等权利，所以这些都是隐藏的
x1 and then give right to given X 2 etc etc all right so these are the hidden
etc all right so these are the hidden States you want to compute these are the
您要计算的状态就是您可以认为它们的观测值
States you want to compute these are the observations you can think of them as
observations you can think of them as noisy or you know there are basically
嘈杂，或者，如果您喜欢在某些情况下，您知道x基本上存在嘈杂的值
noisy or you know there are basically noisy values of x if you like in some
noisy values of x if you like in some sense if the dynamics and the
感觉动力学和观测模型是否正在看到这一点
sense if the dynamics and the observation models are now seeing this
observation models are now seeing this problem has a very nice analytical
这个问题有一个很好的解析解决方案，就是卡尔曼滤波器
problem has a very nice analytical solution that's what the Kalman filter
solution that's what the Kalman filter is all right but you can it can be a
没关系，但是您可以混合使用高斯，也可以是任何东西，
is all right but you can it can be a mixture of gaussians can be anything and
mixture of gaussians can be anything and actually we know how to deal with all of
实际上，我们知道如何处理所有这些问题，并且我们将对这些问题进行处理
actually we know how to deal with all of these problems and we will problem these
these problems and we will problem these things later on but this is what I
后来发生的事情，但这是我想向您展示的，还有更多这样的事情
things later on but this is what I wanted to show you there's more those so
wanted to show you there's more those so when you say dynamics you go from X hat
当您说动力学时，您从X hat减1到XI显然会给我
when you say dynamics you go from X hat minus 1 to X I obviously give that I
minus 1 to X I obviously give that I have to define this distribution and
必须定义此分布，通常是您定义它的方式
have to define this distribution and usually the way you will define it it's
usually the way you will define it it's a Gaussian you can have some unknown
高斯，你可以有一些未知的参数，如均值和方差
a Gaussian you can have some unknown parameters like mean and variance to
parameters like mean and variance to things like that and similarly for the
诸如此类的事情，以及类似的观察模型，您将拥有
things like that and similarly for the observation model you're going to have
observation model you're going to have some unknown parameters okay and you
可以使用一些未知的参数，并且您知道这是我定义方法的恐惧
some unknown parameters okay and you know this fear the way that I define the
know this fear the way that I define the state space model is that this parameter
状态空间模型是该参数表示状态时间，该参数表示它们是
state space model is that this parameter state time this parameters sigh they are
state time this parameters sigh they are stared from other conditional
一直盯着其他条件分布
stared from other conditional distributions across the time so
distributions across the time so basically the parameters that define
基本上是定义动力学模型的参数，或者我去
basically the parameters that define that say the dynamical model or I go
that say the dynamical model or I go from X 1 to X 2 and X 3 to X 2 X 3
从X 1到X 2和X 3到X 2 X 3等参数PI相同
from X 1 to X 2 and X 3 to X 2 X 3 etcetera the parameters PI are the same
etcetera the parameters PI are the same okay so this is sort of where the school
好吧，这是学校知道您下雨的地方，所以您可以使用
okay so this is sort of where the school vomited rain you know so you use the
vomited rain you know so you use the same parameters to describe the dynamics
使用相同的参数来描述动力学，使用相同的参数来定义动力学
same parameters to describe the dynamics and the same parameters to define the
and the same parameters to define the observations obviously not very
观察显然不是很现实，对吧，你可以认为你知道
observations obviously not very realistic right you can think you know
realistic right you can think you know it's not alive but gross normal emotions
它不是活着的，而是正常的情感，但是某些事物并没有加速或
it's not alive but gross normal emotions but something is not accelerating or
but something is not accelerating or something happens it's not spoiling so
发生的事情不会破坏您的期望，所以您不会期望有相同的动态
something happens it's not spoiling so you don't expect the same dynamics at
you don't expect the same dynamics at all the time so this profit is obviously
一直以来，这种利润显然必须随着时间而改变，但是如果您
all the time so this profit is obviously have to change with time but if you
have to change with time but if you really want a trivial case this is how
真的想要一个微不足道的情况，这就是图形模型看起来不错的样子
really want a trivial case this is how the graphical model would look like ok
the graphical model would look like ok and when I wanted to point on this
当我想指出此图时，这将尝试
and when I wanted to point on this diagram and this is going to attempt to
diagram and this is going to attempt to be a problem later on in the course is
在课程的稍后部分是一个问题，当您查看此定向图形时
be a problem later on in the course is when you look at this directed graphical
when you look at this directed graphical model it just loops so on one hand you
建模只是循环，所以一方面您使用相同的参数，所以显然
model it just loops so on one hand you use the same parameters so obviously you
use the same parameters so obviously you save with lots of computation seems like
节省大量计算工作似乎就像您知道的那样，我们将讨论
save with lots of computation seems like you know we will see this one we discuss
you know we will see this one we discuss inference but on the other hand you can
推论，但另一方面，您会看到存在循环，而循环不是
inference but on the other hand you can see there are loops and loops are not
see there are loops and loops are not good for you ok loops are not good for
对你有好处，好的循环对你不好，我的意思是至少如果你
good for you ok loops are not good for you I mean at least the loops if you
you I mean at least the loops if you remove the arrows right you can see
正确删除箭头，您会看到有确定的循环，这将创建
remove the arrows right you can see there are loops ok and this will create
there are loops ok and this will create it will make inference to leave it more
它将使推理比确定上的确定要昂贵得多
it will make inference to leave it more expensive than that one ok on the
expensive than that one ok on the state-space models you can have multiple
状态空间模型，您可以有多个链，您可以在此处查看示例
state-space models you can have multiple chains and you can see an example here
chains and you can see an example here of a factorial state space model so if
阶乘状态空间模型的模型，因此，如果您认为每个隐藏的模型
of a factorial state space model so if you think that each of these hidden
you think that each of these hidden states on the first chain can take em
第一链上的状态可以采用em值，而这可以采用以下em值
states on the first chain can take em values and this can take em values of
values and this can take em values of this prime so you basically have n cube
这个素数，所以您基本上在那时拥有n个多维数据集配置，并且它来了
this prime so you basically have n cube configurations at its time and it comes
configurations at its time and it comes out this is the only message I wanted to
这是我想在这里向您展示的唯一信息是，如果您有
out this is the only message I wanted to show you here is that if you have a
show you here is that if you have a model that looks complicated like that
看起来很复杂的模型，实际上它必须便宜一些才能进行推理
model that looks complicated like that it actually must cheaper to do inference
it actually must cheaper to do inference than having one chain that has m2 the
而不是拥有一个具有m2立方体配置的链
than having one chain that has m2 the cube configurations
cube configurations all right so here I have my views have
好的，所以我在这里拥有最大的土地价值，所以我有F
all right so here I have my views have widest possible land values so I have F
widest possible land values so I have F to the Q possible States if I talk to
到Q个可能的国家，如果我只用一个链来讨论这个问题，就可以将它们带到
to the Q possible States if I talk to this with one chain only can take em to
this with one chain only can take em to the Q values right
Q值正确，这是更复杂的问题
the Q values right that's way much more complicated problem
that's way much more complicated problem because he's empty the cube like thing
因为他空着立方体之类的东西，所以我们将对此进行讨论
because he's empty the cube like thing and so we will discuss about this
and so we will discuss about this factorial state space model so maybe
阶乘状态空间模型，所以也许我们会给您打电话的模式
factorial state space model so maybe we'll give you a call mode to work on
we'll give you a call mode to work on later on in the course again we will do
在本课程的稍后部分，我们将再次详细说明它们并进行推断。
later on in the course again we will do all the details and inference of them on
all the details and inference of them on this type of things maybe in three
这种类型的事情可能会在三堂课或四堂课中出现
this type of things maybe in three lectures or four lectures we'll come
lectures or four lectures we'll come back to his problem alright so I'm going
回到他的问题好了，所以我将从上周开始上课
back to his problem alright so I'm going to take the lecture from last week with
to take the lecture from last week with one very specific example of inference
当图形中的所有内容都是
one very specific example of inference when everything in the graph is
when everything in the graph is described so what is not described I
描述，所以没有描述我有条件概率
described so what is not described I have the conditional probability
have the conditional probability distributions but the actual values of
分布，但您知道的实际值基本上是我们提供的
distributions but the actual values of the you know we provide basically
the you know we provide basically information data for the actual
随机变量实际实现中的信息数据
information data for the actual realizations of random variables in the
realizations of random variables in the nodes of the graph okay and I'm going to
图的节点还可以，我将解决这个问题
nodes of the graph okay and I'm going to address this problem
address this problem not in this slide but the next slide I'm
不是在这张幻灯片中，而是在下一张幻灯片中，我将做一个示例，其中所有
not in this slide but the next slide I'm going to do an example where all the
going to do an example where all the variables are discrete and I will give
变量是离散的，我将为您提供非常具体的计算形式
variables are discrete and I will give you very specific sort of calculation in
you very specific sort of calculation in in two slides on how things look like so
在两张有关事物外观的幻灯片中，所以我们有一张图表给了我
in two slides on how things look like so we have a graph where I have given you
we have a graph where I have given you any realization of the nodes of the
节点的任意变量的值的任何实现
any realization of the nodes of the values of the random variables of the
values of the random variables of the nodes so it's realization is over to you
节点，所以它的实现已经结束，或者没有，我给大家大家都知道
nodes so it's realization is over to you or it's no and I give you everybody know
or it's no and I give you everybody know so there is no missing data here all
所以这里没有丢失的数据，好吧，我完全描述您所知道的
so there is no missing data here all right I describe completely you know for
right I describe completely you know for its higher give you all the baggage of
其较高的价格给您所有消费税，因此模型的逻辑性如此
its higher give you all the baggage of excise so the logical of the model so
excise so the logical of the model so the means data here we're going to use
此处的均值数据我们将在核心中使用它作为一种表示法
the means data here we're going to use this as a notation in the core
this as a notation in the core people would be the unknown parameters
人将成为成为有条件的未知参数
people would be the unknown parameters that became the conditional
that became the conditional distributions in the graph which we
图中的分布，我们不知道它们是什么，所以
distributions in the graph which we don't know what they are so the
don't know what they are so the likelihood is assuming iid data right is
可能性是假设iid数据权是给定theta xi的X i的概率
likelihood is assuming iid data right is the probability of X i given theta x i
the probability of X i given theta x i again is the app data cased and evolves
再次对应用程序数据进行了大小写，并演变了图中的所有注释，然后
again is the app data cased and evolves all the notes in the graph and then what
all the notes in the graph and then what I do is I use the factorization of the
我要做的是我使用图的因式分解来写X i的概率
I do is I use the factorization of the graph to write the probability of X i
graph to write the probability of X i given theta as the power over all nodes
给定theta作为所有情况下I的概率的所有节点上的幂
given theta as the power over all nodes of the probability of for the I case of
of the probability of for the I case of no T given its parents and the
没有T给出其父母和参数theta
no T given its parents and the parameters theta
parameters theta nothing can see right in directive jobs
在指令性工作中什么也看不到对，所以再次，我的意思是
nothing can see right in directive jobs right so again the I means that's the
right so again the I means that's the beta case I so you can remove I when you
测试用例I，因此当您以第二种方式想到第二个术语时，可以删除我
beta case I so you can remove I when you think of the second term the way we
think of the second term the way we factorized is the property is the
因数分解是属性是概率的乘积
factorized is the property is the product of the probabilities of the
product of the probabilities of the facts that is not given the its parents
没有给它的父母和你有逗号的参数的事实
facts that is not given the its parents and you have comma the parameters
and you have comma the parameters because we don't know where the
因为我们不知道公里在哪里，所以我现在要做什么
because we don't know where the kilometers are so what I'm gonna do now
kilometers are so what I'm gonna do now is I am going to reverse to reverse the
我将要反向以反转节点和产品上的产品
is I am going to reverse to reverse the product over the node and the product
product over the node and the product over the dataset so I'm going to put the
在数据集上，所以我将产品放在内部的数据集上，
over the dataset so I'm going to put the product over the data sets inside and
product over the data sets inside and some we have this point of outside and
一些我们有外部的观点，然后是数据集上的乘积，甚至
some we have this point of outside and then the product over the data set even
then the product over the data set even be operating on the probability of XIT
给定父母为T的IPS并以XIT的概率进行运算
be operating on the probability of XIT given the parents for the IPS of T and
given the parents for the IPS of T and the parameters theta and I call this the
参数theta，我称之为与节点族最好的参数
the parameters theta and I call this the best associated with the family of node
best associated with the family of node P isn't in fact the likelihood of the
P实际上不是家庭的可能性
P isn't in fact the likelihood of the family
family the likelihood of the data over the
数据在无T族中的可能性，因此，如果您将其移动
the likelihood of the data over the family of no T so if you move this
family of no T so if you move this outside right then you put it here
在外面，然后将其放在所有节点上的乘积中，并将其放置在此处
outside right then you put it here product over all the nodes and it here
product over all the nodes and it here this refers to T an exponent so isn't it
这是指T的指数，所以这不是真的喜剧的可能性吗？
this refers to T an exponent so isn't it really the likelihood of the comedy of
really the likelihood of the comedy of know T it only involves the data that
知道它只涉及与最薄森林有关的数据
know T it only involves the data that have to do with thinnest forest
基本上，当你看这个等式时，谁能坐得正确
who can sit up right so basically when you look at this equation like what does
you look at this equation like what does it do what can we say for the level of
对于该公式中超过的可能性水平，我们可以说什么
it do what can we say for the level of likelihood in this formula that is over
在注释上，所以即使您有一个非常复杂的图表，
over the notes so even though you have a very complicated diagram right the
very complicated diagram right the likelihood okay of the data it arises
数据出现的可能性还可以超过我何时知道的可能性
likelihood okay of the data it arises over the likelihood you know when I
over the likelihood you know when I stayed with the knowledge were in it's
留在其中的知识不包括该节点的社区
stayed with the knowledge were in it's not include the community of that node
not include the community of that node because V is the likelihood of the
因为V是那个知道的家庭的可能性，这是为什么
because V is the likelihood of the family of that know and why is this
family of that know and why is this important because it tells you that this
重要，因为它告诉您这个问题是每个节点P可以
important because it tells you that this problem is theta P for each node P can
problem is theta P for each node P can be computed separately for the parameter
对于泡菜人天鹅或健身P的参数分别计算
be computed separately for the parameter which a pickle people Swan or fitness P
which a pickle people Swan or fitness P plus 2 so you can actually compute the
加2，因此您实际上可以在本地为其音符计算参数，因为
plus 2 so you can actually compute the parameters locally for its note because
parameters locally for its note because they decouple the way this to be the
当您有不完整的数据但他们将这种方式解耦时，
they decouple the way this to be the case when you have incomplete data but
case when you have incomplete data but now I do notice if from this equation if
现在我确实从这个等式中注意到，如果您有完整的数据，您会得到一个产品
now I do notice if from this equation if you have complete data you get a product
you have complete data you get a product of terms solids
固体不行，所以配方会分解
of terms solids no okay so the recipe would decompose
no okay so the recipe would decompose the quality the graphs left okay and if
图形的质量还可以，如果您想知道盲目可能性
the quality the graphs left okay and if you want you know to go blind likelihood
you want you know to go blind likelihood then you want to introduce a prior for
那么您想为参数引入先验，就可以做一个简单的
then you want to introduce a prior for the parameters you can make a simple
the parameters you can make a simple assumption that the prior of the
假设参数排序支持的先验到达
assumption that the prior of the parameter sort support arrives over the
parameter sort support arrives over the nodes so basically this makes sense
节点，所以基本上这是合理的，因为您的分布
nodes so basically this makes sense right because you the distribution for
right because you the distribution for the Rises and you have every conditional
上升，您将有一个带节点的引导的所有条件分布
the Rises and you have every conditional distribution of leading with a node
distribution of leading with a node having this theta T so you can put a
有了这个theta T，所以你可以放一个先验但像这样的循环然后
having this theta T so you can put a prior but loops like that and then the
prior but loops like that and then the posterior
后部狐狸也出现在音符上，所以
posterior Fox arises over notes as well right so
Fox arises over notes as well right so if you can do Bayesian inference to
如果可以进行贝叶斯推断以计算theta T RT，请单独注意
if you can do Bayesian inference to compute theta T RT to note separately
compute theta T RT to note separately I'm going to give you a very specific
我很快会给你一个非常具体的例子，但这有点
I'm going to give you a very specific example soon okay but this to sort of
example soon okay but this to sort of equations are extremely important here
方程在这里非常重要
轻描淡写，只有当您有完整的数据描述时，
example soon okay but this to sort of equations are extremely important here
make any bit of tact this is only when you have complete data describe if there
轻描淡写，只有当您有完整的数据描述时，
you have complete data describe if there are missing data this is not the case
缺少数据，情况并非如此，所以您知道他们说这是一个
are missing data this is not the case all right so you know they said it's a
all right so you know they said it's a different story that we will see later
不同的故事，我们将在稍后看到，但这有点琐碎
different story that we will see later on but this is sort of a very trivial
on but this is sort of a very trivial case if you have complete data you can
如果您有完整的数据，则可以推断出参数是什么
case if you have complete data you can infer what the parameters are
infer what the parameters are by using this decomposition of the
通过使用后验侦探的分解图
by using this decomposition of the posterior detective the over the graph
在下一张幻灯片上，您将看到数字，如果您不理解此示例，
on the next slide you will see numbers so if you don't understand this example
so if you don't understand this example you will understand hopefully the slides
希望您会理解咨询的幻灯片，因为它具有特定的
you will understand hopefully the slides of counseling because it has specific
of counseling because it has specific numbers so let me add some when I
数字，所以当我考虑有条件的情况时，让我添加一些
numbers so let me add some when I consider the case where the conditional
consider the case where the conditional probabilities are given in terms of
概率以表格的形式给出，所以我们在谈论
probabilities are given in terms of tables all right so we're talking about
tables all right so we're talking about discrete variables practically valuable
离散变量对遵循多重新分布具有实际价值，因此
discrete variables practically valuable to follow a multi newly distribution so
to follow a multi newly distribution so let me see what that word eternal final
让我看看那个词永恒的最终分布在这里，我在看没有T
let me see what that word eternal final distribution Here I am looking at no T
distribution Here I am looking at no T and I say the probability of the given
我说给定指数的概率是
and I say the probability of the given exponent is a categorical of
exponent is a categorical of multi-annual distribution with
参数为θTC的多年期分布，因此下标
multi-annual distribution with parameters theta T C so the subscripts
parameters theta T C so the subscripts Elstree have a minute here please we
Elstree在这里有一分钟，请我们了解一下Syst值
Elstree have a minute here please we know that the looking Syst the value the
know that the looking Syst the value the parents are
父母是
所以基本上您可以互相感谢对方的价值观
know that the looking Syst the value the parents are
so basically you can thank each other responding to the values of their
所以基本上您可以互相感谢对方的价值观
responding to the values of their parents okay and then what you do is you
父母好吧，然后您要做的是，您符合分类分布，所以
parents okay and then what you do is you fit a categorical distribution okay so
fit a categorical distribution okay so the probability of T given its balance
考虑到T处于状态C的T的概率是分类的
the probability of T given its balance being a state C is a categorical
being a state C is a categorical distribution and obviously in this
分布，显然在这种分类分布中，您还记得
distribution and obviously in this categorical distribution you remember
categorical distribution you remember they're going to have an opportunity of
他们将有一个国家的机会，如果你在整个阶段总结一下
they're going to have an opportunity of State and if you sum over all the stage
State and if you sum over all the stage this Thetas there for some to R T
这个Thetas在那里有一些RT可以参加，就像你基本上
this Thetas there for some to R T participate as you basically the
participate as you basically the probability of being theta T C 1 is the
成为TC 1的概率是处于状态1的概率
probability of being theta T C 1 is the probability of being in state 1
probability of being in state 1 disappears the probability of being in
消失了处于状态T的可能性，因此，如果将所有这些总和相加，
disappears the probability of being in state T so if you sum all of this you
state T so if you sum all of this you get 1 but remember it appreciates the
等于1，但请记住，它赞赏在节点3处成为状态K的可能性
get 1 but remember it appreciates the probability of being state K at node 3
probability of being state K at node 3 given that the parents are in state C
鉴于父母都处于C状态，所以基本上你不能说我的意思
given that the parents are in state C right so basically you cannot say I mean
right so basically you cannot say I mean you can't do the modular calculation if
如果需要，您不能进行模块化计算，但是在这里
you can't do the modular calculation if you want to but here too
you want to but here too we're going to the table tell us the
我们将在表中告诉我们在给定状态下3的概率
we're going to the table tell us the probability of 3 given the state of the
probability of 3 given the state of the parents all right and we pick this with
家长，好的，我们选择该类别并对其进行分类
parents all right and we pick this with a categorical distribution of this
a categorical distribution of this parameters with this normalization so
归一化的参数，所以让我们显式地写出theta D CK
parameters with this normalization so let's write this explicitly theta D CK
let's write this explicitly theta D CK is the probability P means again 90 okay
是P再次表示90的概率好吗，我们在90
is the probability P means again 90 okay we're working at 90
we're working at 90 so it's no it has its own conditional
所以不是，它有自己的条件概率，所以p ck是概率
so it's no it has its own conditional probability so p ck is the probability
probability so p ck is the probability that X days it takes the value K when
在X天里，当植物可以接受修道院的时候，其价值为K。
that X days it takes the value K when the plants can take the monastry the
the plants can take the monastry the sequence of the industries here it's
此处的行业顺序是任意权利，您可以将其反转
sequence of the industries here it's arbitrary right you could have reverse
arbitrary right you could have reverse it so this is the notation used here
所以这是这里使用的符号，节点K是
it so this is the notation used here there is the node K is the value that
there is the node K is the value that the XT will take given that the parents
假设父母处于状态3，XT会采取
the XT will take given that the parents are in state 3
are in state 3 we're going to assume that they're Katy
我们将假设他们是凯蒂州
we're going to assume that they're Katy States for
States for no T we're going to ask you that the
不，我们要问您父母可以属于持有人类别
no T we're going to ask you that the parents can be at categories of holder
parents can be at categories of holder City Sacramento City and City is what is
萨克拉曼多市市区和城市的便士是多少钱你有多少父母
City Sacramento City and City is what is the penny how many parents you have is
the penny how many parents you have is the product basically of the states of
基本上是贫穷国家的产品，所以今晚有两个父母
the product basically of the states of the poverty so tonight has two parents
the poverty so tonight has two parents at this point just to polish this just
在这一点上，只是擦亮这三个将是2乘以3
at this point just to polish this just three will be 2 times 3
好的，我将在一个具体示例中向您展示，但是基本上这是
okay again I will show you this in a specific example but basically this is
specific example but basically this is the the house is discrete distributions
房子是离散分布，这个条件概率是
the the house is discrete distributions this conditional probabilities are
this conditional probabilities are defined using a multi newly or
使用多个新分布或分类分布进行定义，因此我们
defined using a multi newly or categorical distribution so what we're
categorical distribution so what we're gonna do is and now you know I expect
现在要做的是，现在您知道我希望至少您有一些基本知识
gonna do is and now you know I expect that at least you have some elementary
that at least you have some elementary understanding of a d-flat distribution
如果您不给我发送电子邮件，您将了解D-flat分布
understanding of a d-flat distribution if you not send me an e-mail you'll know
if you not send me an e-mail you'll know who sent you a few pages from maybe
谁从Bishop的书中寄了几页给您，还是让这本书读起来
who sent you a few pages from maybe Bishop's book or make this book to read
Bishop's book or make this book to read whether it's really the distribution is
是否真的是分布是此多重之前的共轭
whether it's really the distribution is the the conjugate prior to this multi
the the conjugate prior to this multi annually distribution so each of this
每年的分布，因此每个参数都收集向量
annually distribution so each of this parameters they collect the vector that
parameters they collect the vector that involves all these people district a
涉及所有这些人的地区，我们将提出一个非常明确的先决条件
involves all these people district a we're going to put a very clear prior
we're going to put a very clear prior alright and then because they are
好的，然后因为给定了数据D，所以它们是共轭的
alright and then because they are conjugate the posterior given the data D
conjugate the posterior given the data D is going to come up to be a vehicular
将成为具有参数的车辆分布
is going to come up to be a vehicular distribution with parameters cannot
distribution with parameters cannot deceive defined from the prior plus MT
从先验加MT定义的欺骗，请参见这是矢量右喷雾器的位置
deceive defined from the prior plus MT see where this is a vector right mister
see where this is a vector right mister vector and this is a vector and here's
向量，这是向量，这是向量的定义，所以我要
vector and this is a vector and here's the definition of the vector so I want
the definition of the vector so I want you to look at it and tell me what this
您看看它，然后告诉我这基本上是使用常识语言的
you to look at it and tell me what this is using common sense language basically
is using common sense language basically P is the 90 K is the probability that
P是90 K是宣布主体为注释II的值可以的概率
P is the 90 K is the probability that declares the body a value of note II can
declares the body a value of note II can take assuming that the parents are in in
假设父母处于状态C，那么np ck是什么
take assuming that the parents are in in state C so what is n p ck
state C so what is n p ck in my data set because carol have
在我的数据集中，因为卡罗尔放逐了我将可能性乘以
in my data set because carol have banished I multiply the likelihood with
banished I multiply the likelihood with this prior so what do you think PC case
因此，您如何看待PC机箱，您可以在这里看一下患者
this prior so what do you think PC case and you can look at the patient here is
and you can look at the patient here is the number of times in my data set the
我的数据集中否定的次数是处于什么状态而不是
the number of times in my data set the negative is in what state instead of
negative is in what state instead of Terry given that the parents are in
特里（Terry）考虑到父母的状态为C，所以这是经验性的
Terry given that the parents are in state C okay so that's the empirical
state C okay so that's the empirical count I mean this is sort of if you
伯爵我的意思是，这有点像，如果你看这是兄弟，实际上
count I mean this is sort of if you watch this is brother actually there's
watch this is brother actually there's no algebraic just like you know you know
就像您知道的一样，没有代数，所以这足够了
no algebraic just like you know you know so this is sort of the sufficient
so this is sort of the sufficient statistics for this problem so it's a
此问题的统计数据，因此它是数据科学家指标的国家
statistics for this problem so it's a nation of the data scientists indicator
nation of the data scientists indicator function and counts the time senior data
函数并计算时间T的高级数据集，其中没有T处于状态k
function and counts the time senior data set that no T is in state k given that
set that no T is in state k given that it's parents are in state C so the the
它的父母处于C状态，因此每日平均分配
it's parents are in state C so the the mean of the distribution the daily
mean of the distribution the daily distribution basically there has if you
分布基本上有，如果您在Wikipedia上查看，将会看到
distribution basically there has if you check on Wikipedia will see what the
check on Wikipedia will see what the meanest is for example for this
例如，平均而言，此分布为50 GK除以
meanest is for example for this distribution is 50 G K divided by the
distribution is 50 G K divided by the summation of alpha T C K prime for all
所有磁带行的alpha TCK素数的总和，因此
summation of alpha T C K prime for all tape lines so the mean of the
tape lines so the mean of the distribution of the posterior comes to
后验分布就是这个关键计数加上alpha D CK
distribution of the posterior comes to be this critical count plus alpha D CK
be this critical count plus alpha D CK from the prior and then in the numerator
从先验，然后在分子分母中，您实际上有
from the prior and then in the numerator denominator you have this actually
denominator you have this actually should be inside parentheses you know
应该在您知道的括号内，即使在这里很明显，所以这
should be inside parentheses you know even though it's obvious here so this
even though it's obvious here so this whole automation here count over K prime
这里的整个自动化超过K素数，所以如果您说您使用了非预期的
whole automation here count over K prime so if let's say you use an unintended
so if let's say you use an unintended clip I or where all the surface are
夹住I或所有表面都等于1的情况
clip I or where all the surface are equal to one so actively this is sort of
equal to one so actively this is sort of regularization so you just add one in
正则化，所以您只需在所有经验值中加一个
regularization so you just add one in all the empirical counts so if let's say
all the empirical counts so if let's say foreign state
外国你没有测量宇宙说
foreign state you have no measurements universe say
you have no measurements universe say that they would never happen
他们永远不会发生天鹅你使它成为可能，那是
that they would never happen Swan you make it possible and that's
Swan you make it possible and that's what this thing does it sort of the
这个东西对直方图有什么作用是这种类型的问题
what this thing does it sort of the histogram is this problem for this type
histogram is this problem for this type of prevents well let's see an example so
的预防措施很好，让我们来看一个例子，所以我们有一个直接阻止
of prevents well let's see an example so this is so we have a direct block with
this is so we have a direct block with five nodes and let's say we get some
五个节点，假设我们得到了一些数据
five nodes and let's say we get some data
all right and the database will contain the realizations of X 1 X 2 X 3 X 4 X 5
好的，数据库将包含X 1 X 2 X 3 X 4 X 5的实现
the realizations of X 1 X 2 X 3 X 4 X 5 and we have I am going to I think
我想我想很明显，在这种情况下，二元体运动
and we have I am going to I think obviously the binary body motion in this
obviously the binary body motion in this problem of forgot to mention obviously
问题显然忘记了提及，所以过程是0 0 1 0 0 1 1 1和
problem of forgot to mention obviously so the process is 0 0 1 0 0 1 1 1 and
so the process is 0 0 1 0 0 1 1 1 and Here I am
这是我在数据集中所占的比重，这不是
Here I am counts in my data set where no this is
counts in my data set where no this is what this here is from stage 1 or stage
假设零件处于状态C，这是阶段1或阶段0的结果
what this here is from stage 1 or stage 0 given that the parts are in state C
0 given that the parts are in state C which is defined on the rolls on the
它在左侧的卷上定义，您会看到确定，所以让我们
which is defined on the rolls on the left hand side you see that ok so let's
left hand side you see that ok so let's look at the case when the parents are at
看父母在1 1的情况下多少次看数据集
look at the case when the parents are at 1 1 how many times look at the data set
1 1 how many times look at the data set when X 2 next year of at 1 how many
当下一年的X 2等于K的多少倍K知道第一个节点位于
when X 2 next year of at 1 how many times K the know T the first node is at
times K the know T the first node is at 1 so I see one case here and I see two
1所以我在这里看到一种情况，而我们看到了两种
1 so I see one case here and I see two we do
同样地，让我们看看音符有多少次
similarly let's see how many times the note
note is a k equal to 0 when this is 1 and 1
等于1和1时ak等于0 2 1 1 0 1好的
is a k equal to 0 when this is 1 and 1 the 2 1 1 0 1 okay
the 2 1 1 0 1 okay 21 and so we can either they say the
21，所以我们可以说如果您不这样做，则概率为a
21 and so we can either they say the probability if you don't do this a
probability if you don't do this a priori and you use the MLE estimate the
先验，然后您使用MLE估计概率，或者说v pc k等于
priori and you use the MLE estimate the probability let's say or v pc k equal to
probability let's say or v pc k equal to 1 I mean I should actually I hope I
1我的意思是我实际上应该希望我不要混淆您的意思我的意思350
1 I mean I should actually I hope I don't confuse you care what I mean 350
don't confuse you care what I mean 350 see k equal to 1 I mean pick up this G 1
看到k等于1我的意思是捡起这个G 1就是我的意思，所以
see k equal to 1 I mean pick up this G 1 that's what I mean okay so the
that's what I mean okay so the probability of P that is T 1 the mean
P的概率为T 1如果不做，则不做平均值
probability of P that is T 1 the mean value if you don't do if you don't put
value if you don't do if you don't put any prior will be let's say 2 divided by
之前的任何事都可以用2除以3来表示，但请记住，我们必须添加
any prior will be let's say 2 divided by 3 but remember we have to add on the
3 but remember we have to add on the previous diagram if we use the clave
上图，如果我们使用系数为1的先验分布
previous diagram if we use the clave distributions prior with coefficient 1
distributions prior with coefficient 1 we have to add 1 to the counts so it
我们必须将1加到计数上，所以它将被3除以5，这将是
we have to add 1 to the counts so it will be 3 divided by 5 and here will be
will be 3 divided by 5 and here will be 1 plus 1 2 divided by 5
1加1 2除以5好
1 plus 1 2 divided by 5 alright
显然，变量是离散的，所以您知道这么复杂，但是
obviously the variables are discrete you know so such a complicated but in
know so such a complicated but in essence you know even if the
本质上，即使分布是高斯分布或存在
essence you know even if the distributions were Gaussian or there are
distributions were Gaussian or there are something else you can do stimuli to
您可以通过其他方法刺激您知道的想法，并进行完整的贝叶斯方法
something else you can do stimuli to ideas you know and and do full Bayesian
ideas you know and and do full Bayesian analysis to compute the the parameters
分析以计算条件分布中的参数
analysis to compute the the parameters in the conditional distribution now in
in the conditional distribution now in currency girls right you don't know
货币女孩，对，您通常不知道，您知道您拥有的其他节点
currency girls right you don't know usually other nodes you know you have
usually other nodes you know you have personal data so you know some things
个人数据，所以您知道一些事情，而您却不知道所有事情，所以这
personal data so you know some things you don't know all the things so this
you don't know all the things so this could be the real problem we have to
可能是真正的问题，我们必须在此类中处理，但是如果您完成
could be the real problem we have to deal in this class but if your complete
deal in this class but if your complete data it's an easy problem and actually
数据，这是一个简单的问题，实际上您知道例如谁使用的产品
data it's an easy problem and actually you know if products for example who use
you know if products for example who use simulation to generate a lots of data
模拟以生成大量数据，然后将它们拟合为这两个模型
simulation to generate a lots of data and then they fit these two models you
and then they fit these two models you know you may have the case indeed what
知道您可能确实遇到了您在图中描述的情况
know you may have the case indeed what you described in the graph
you described in the graph you know everything or item karakuri
您知道一切或物品卡拉库里的抵抗力，因此您可以使用这种类型的
you know everything or item karakuri resistance so you can use this type of
resistance so you can use this type of organization so let me drink some coffee
组织，所以让我喝点咖啡，然后我们改变主题
organization so let me drink some coffee and then we change subject
今天我给星巴克装了咖啡，因为他们告诉我咖啡加起来
today I fitted up the Starbucks because they told me that coffee went up to
they told me that coffee went up to three or five and I said since when
三五点，我说，因为昨天我在那儿的时候，他们
three or five and I said since when because I was there yesterday then they
because I was there yesterday then they said to me are you kiddin and I said of
对我说你是孩子吗？我当然对95说
said to me are you kiddin and I said of course then to 95
所以你知道也许明天你们伙计给我四处走走学生证，这样我就可以
so you know maybe tomorrow you guys give me go around your student card so I can
me go around your student card so I can hit it you know and get my discount what
打它，你知道并得到我的折扣，这就像歧视是什么
hit it you know and get my discount what is that it's like discrimination is it
我会再次见到我，他们基本上是在踏板车上问您三件事
I'm going to see me again they asked you on the scooter basically three things we
on the scooter basically three things we already have seen and then try to
已经看过，然后尝试介绍一些概念，但是我们使
already have seen and then try to introduce some concepts but we make the
introduce some concepts but we make the elimination over basically easily to
基本上可以轻松消除编程问题，我将要做一些
elimination over basically easily to program I'm gonna do something sort of a
program I'm gonna do something sort of a little bit stupid but you know we're all
有点愚蠢，但你知道我们都已经成熟，所以你知道我要带
little bit stupid but you know we're all mature so you know I'm gonna bring maybe
mature so you know I'm gonna bring maybe if not today
如果不是今天星期四，则不应该由
if not today on on Thursday one shouldn't directed by
on on Thursday one shouldn't directed by really discussing some details because I
真的在讨论一些细节，因为我不想将本次演讲分为
really discussing some details because I don't want to split this lecture on
don't want to split this lecture on directed graphs and then three weeks
有向图，然后三个星期后，您会从中得到相同的结果
directed graphs and then three weeks later tell you the same things from
later tell you the same things from directed ok so I'm gonna sit in some
指示确定，所以我将坐在一些您需要了解的信息中
directed ok so I'm gonna sit in some information that you need to know about
information that you need to know about undirected graphs and discuss this
无向图，并讨论这个消除算法，您可以
undirected graphs and discuss this elimination algorithm you can he'll
elimination algorithm you can he'll think of some notes that would describe
想到一些描述它们的音符，所以这是加粗的Aryan，这些是
think of some notes that would describe them so this is bolded Aryan these are
them so this is bolded Aryan these are the evidence no notes these are the
没有证据的证据这些是查询节点，这就是您想要的
the evidence no notes these are the query nodes right this is what you want
query nodes right this is what you want to compute and there are some hidden
计算并有一些隐藏的注释，您知道是否要
to compute and there are some hidden notes and you know if you want to
notes and you know if you want to complete them you can complete them but
完成它们，您可以完成它们，但是在这里，我要做的就是
complete them you can complete them but here what I'm gonna do is I'm gonna
here what I'm gonna do is I'm gonna quite hidden noise because you don't
相当隐蔽的噪音，因为您不在乎一切，所以积极地
quite hidden noise because you don't care about all right so actively this is
care about all right so actively this is your Q K X 1 given X ticks and you can
您的QKX 1给定X滴答声，您可以全部知道自己不知道
your Q K X 1 given X ticks and you can all of this knows that you don't know so
all of this knows that you don't know so what you need to do is integrate them
您需要做的就是将它们整合起来，我想我们已经拥有了
what you need to do is integrate them out and I think we already have
out and I think we already have discussed that the big picture basically
讨论了大图基本上看起来像您在
discussed that the big picture basically looks like the equation you see on the
looks like the equation you see on the on the bottle alright so we want to
好在瓶子上，所以我们要计算给定X的概率
on the bottle alright so we want to compute the probability of X hath given
compute the probability of X hath given the X the evidence and I write this as
X是证据，我将其写为XF和XT的联合概率，
the X the evidence and I write this as the joint probability of X F and X T and
the joint probability of X F and X T and that probability can be written as all
那个概率可以写成所有联合所有的所有概率
that probability can be written as all the probability of all the joint all the
the probability of all the joint all the body moves with the hidden variables
阀体与隐藏变量集成的阀一起运动，然后在这里
body moves with the hidden variables integrated valve and then here you have
integrated valve and then here you have the probability of ecstasy which means
摇头丸的可能性，这意味着它必须与excel联合
the probability of ecstasy which means it will have to the joint with excel
it will have to the joint with excel four exits integrated out remember that
集成了四个出口，请记住，没有任何幻想可能是轮换
four exits integrated out remember that nothing fancy really may be the rotation
nothing fancy really may be the rotation is slightly different right so that we
是稍微不同的权利，所以我们需要知道这是什么
is slightly different right so that we need to know this is what the
need to know this is what the elimination algorithm is how can we use
消除算法是如何利用乘积理论思想来做的
elimination algorithm is how can we use of the product theoretic ideas to do
of the product theoretic ideas to do this effectively and and I think in some
这很有效，我认为在某些示例中我们强调了这一点
this effectively and and I think in some of the examples we have highlighted this
of the examples we have highlighted this but hopefully today if we managed to
但希望今天如果我们能够完成此任务，我们将看到一些想法
but hopefully today if we managed to finish this we will see some ideas have
finish this we will see some ideas have some graphs don't need absolutist so me
有些图不需要绝对主义者，所以我告诉你这里的主意是
some graphs don't need absolutist so me tell you what the idea is here is we're
tell you what the idea is here is we're going to use the distribution law when
在进行这些求和时将使用分配定律，所以你知道我
going to use the distribution law when we do these summations and so you know I
we do these summations and so you know I give you here an example you have the
这里给你一个例子，你有一些恒定时间XI的总和
give you here an example you have the summation of some constant times X I
summation of some constant times X I obviously you can move that constant R
显然，您可以将常数R移开并说出alpha乘以Sigma XI，所以
obviously you can move that constant R far out and say alpha times Sigma X I so
far out and say alpha times Sigma X I so that's one of the compilations were
这是将要使用的汇编之一，从更一般的意义上讲
that's one of the compilations were going to use and in a more general sense
going to use and in a more general sense if we have summation on you know think
如果我们有求和，就知道x1 xn上的这些离散变量
if we have summation on you know think of these discrete variables on the x1 xn
of these discrete variables on the x1 xn and inside we have alpha 1 X 1 over 2 X
在里面，我们有1 X 1 X 2 X 2等
and inside we have alpha 1 X 1 over 2 X 2 etcetera
2 etcetera look what I have done I took this
看看我做了什么我服用了这款产品，然后将它们分成几部分，
look what I have done I took this product and I split them in pieces and
product and I split them in pieces and then I pushed on with the summations so
然后我继续进行求和，所以每个求和仅在右边进行
then I pushed on with the summations so each of them operates only on the right
each of them operates only on the right argument so if I want to start on extend
参数，所以如果我想开始扩展
argument so if I want to start on extend which
which the point of having the whole number can
具有整数的观点可以节省产品扩展剂的吟时间
the point of having the whole number can save groans time on extender for product
save groans time on extender for product where an X n it only appears from the
X n只能从联邦时间xn出现，所以我有什么
where an X n it only appears from the federal time xn all right so I have what
federal time xn all right so I have what you do this if you push xn all the way
如果您将xn完全推入，则可以执行此操作，这样您就可以使用它了
you do this if you push xn all the way in so you could use this then you
in so you could use this then you compute the summation xn minus 1 and
计算总和xn减去1，然后最终计算
compute the summation xn minus 1 and then eventually you compute the
then eventually you compute the sturbation on xn so the idea is what you
在xn上进行扰动，因此您将在此处看到执行此求和的想法
sturbation on xn so the idea is what you see here for performing this summation
see here for performing this summation that effectively will allow us to
有效地使我们能够有效地做到所有这些边缘化
that effectively will allow us to effectively do this marginalization all
effectively do this marginalization all right this is what the objective is we
对，这就是目标，我们知道这是他们的两个
right this is what the objective is we you know say this are two of their
you know say this are two of their cumulative rings but basically together
累积振铃，但基本上与操作加号和
cumulative rings but basically together with the operations plus and
with the operations plus and multiplication so this is the
乘法，所以这是有效的关联交换律
multiplication so this is the associative commutative law effectively
associative commutative law effectively generalizing for this elements a b c and
对此元素abc进行概括，并对该交换环进行推广，
generalizing for this elements a b c and this commutative ring this property that
this commutative ring this property that you see here this is sort of what we
您会在这里看到这是我们可以利用的优势，所以对于任何荷兰银行（ABN）棍子
you see here this is sort of what we take advantage okay so for any ABN stick
take advantage okay so for any ABN stick where we can do this
在这里我们可以做到这一点，所以必须谨慎
where we can do this so the this one have to be discreet
so the this one have to be discreet mahalo which can be continuous can be
可以连续的玛哈洛你能知道其他奇怪的事情吗
mahalo which can be continuous can be you know other weird things okay this
you know other weird things okay this property if it is valid then we can
属性是否有效，那么我们可以将此想法应用到计算中
property if it is valid then we can apply this this idea for computing
apply this this idea for computing modulation processors okay
调制处理器还可以
现在显然我们希望找到一种进行求和的有效方法
apply this this idea for computing modulation processors okay
now obviously we want to find an effective way for doing the summations
现在显然我们希望找到一种进行求和的有效方法
effective way for doing the summations because let me see if there is account
因为如果您要说的话，让我看看这里是否有帐户
because let me see if there is account here if you let's say that if you want
here if you let's say that if you want to some so in this case the same we want
对于某些情况，在这种情况下，我们希望通过某种方式解决此隐藏变量
to some so in this case the same we want to somehow this hidden variable solve
to somehow this hidden variable solve okay so let's call them the total number
好吧，我们称它们为隐藏变量的总数是Billis all
okay so let's call them the total number of hidden variables is is Billis all
of hidden variables is is Billis all right so obviously the summation of the
对，因此很明显，隐藏变量的总和将导致
right so obviously the summation of the hidden variables will result in the
hidden variables will result in the computation which will be after this
对于可能的数量，将在此幂之后进行计算
computation which will be after this power for either the number of possible
power for either the number of possible values that this monomers can take or
该单体可以吸收或实际上必须消耗一些的值
values that this monomers can take or actually ever have to some dissipation
actually ever have to some dissipation values there are personal values of this
价值观有个人的价值观，对于每个价值观他们都有怪物
values there are personal values of this and for each of this they have monster
and for each of this they have monster one serve out and they are possible of a
一个发球出去，他们是可能的，所以我们是力量
one serve out and they are possible of a list of that so we are to the power
list of that so we are to the power rates and I'm not the kind of thing that
率，我不是那种需要被边缘化的事情
rates and I'm not the kind of thing that you will need to do this marginalization
you will need to do this marginalization for each module itself the of the
对于每个模块本身，受赠机构的工作正常，但这是为了
for each module itself the of the grantee body works okay but this is for
grantee body works okay but this is for the big graph this is a big number and
大图这是一个很大的数字，我们不喜欢它不会
the big graph this is a big number and we don't like it it will not be
we don't like it it will not be efficient to do marginalization right so
做边缘化的效率很高，所以让我们在星型算法中进行讨论
efficient to do marginalization right so let's discuss this in star algorithm
所以我们有更好的选择，如果我们愿意的话，我们想做很多事情，
so we have a better to go and let's say if we want to we want to do much an
if we want to we want to do much an unsession or no deck 6
没有会议，没有甲板6好的，所以我们想做的是，如果可以的话
unsession or no deck 6 ok so what we want to do so if you can
ok so what we want to do so if you can do this in an aviary right so this
用鸟的权利来做这件事，所以这个总结将是六个操作
do this in an aviary right so this summation would be six operations well
summation would be six operations well I'm sorry
很抱歉，如果要进行六次操作，
I'm sorry six operations if this takes on the
six operations if this takes on the values the summation onyx 6 will be our
值onyx 6将是我们对其他每个值的运算
values the summation onyx 6 will be our operations for each of the other values
operations for each of the other values of this and this and this and this will
这个，这个，这个和这个中的一个，基本上是总共六个
of this and this and this and this will be a total basically for to the six
be a total basically for to the six operation ok so let's see a way that
好的操作，让我们来看看这种白色拉链在执行此操作时的方法
operation ok so let's see a way that this way white zipper in performing this
this way white zipper in performing this what we don't do up to the six
在这六项操作中我们没有做的是什么，所以我在这里所做的是
what we don't do up to the six operations so what I have done here is I
operations so what I have done here is I wrote the factorization of the golf
写了高尔夫的因式分解权，给定x1给定x1 x3给定效果
wrote the factorization of the golf right the effects 1 x2 given x1 x3 given
right the effects 1 x2 given x1 x3 given X 2 X 5 given the power that 3x tix
X 2 X 5赋予了3x tix赋予其父母等的力量，然后当我
X 2 X 5 given the power that 3x tix given its parents etc and then when I
given its parents etc and then when I have done is like this the summation on
这样就完成了对X的求和，一直到右边，因为
have done is like this the summation on X takes all the way to the right because
X takes all the way to the right because that's the only place 4 X 6 counts and
那是4 X 6计数的唯一位置，此分布的总和为
that's the only place 4 X 6 counts and the summation of this distribution is
the summation of this distribution is actually equal to 1 because it's a body
实际上等于1，因为它是身体的条件分布
actually equal to 1 because it's a body conditional distribution that is
conditional distribution that is normalized so how much handsome I have
归一化，所以有多少帅哥我必须什么都不做0，所以如果你实际上做
normalized so how much handsome I have to do 0 nothing so if you actually do
to do 0 nothing so if you actually do this you will find yourselves doing
你会发现自己在第六次之后做的时候
this you will find yourselves doing after the 6th when this actually
after the 6th when this actually requires ok it is shown right maybe this
要求确定，它显示正确，也许这不是一个东西
requires ok it is shown right maybe this it is it is not one which is something
it is it is not one which is something else here and if he has 3 arguments the
否则在这里，如果他有3个参数，则求和将是
else here and if he has 3 arguments the doing the summation will be out to a
doing the summation will be out to a power which is way better than out to
胜过第六次幂的能力
power which is way better than out to the sixth power
the sixth power ok so this is what we need to take
好，这就是我们需要利用的地方
ok so this is what we need to take advantage
advantage like there's a lot of a sell-off and
就像有很多抛售，实际上提醒我我要寄给你
like there's a lot of a sell-off and actually remind me I'm going to send you
actually remind me I'm going to send you a copy of absorbance chapter to read
吸光度章节的副本阅读这本书，我从中提取了这么大
a copy of absorbance chapter to read this book where I extracted this big
this book where I extracted this big sirs okay so if I forget to do that not
先生，好吧，如果我忘了做那件事，不是我，因为今天我回家之前，
sirs okay so if I forget to do that not me because the before I go home today so
me because the before I go home today so so again the same problem we want to
因此，同样的问题，我们要计算不，我们要计算
so again the same problem we want to compute no we want to compute a
compute no we want to compute a summation with a spectrum of Pi it's
用Pi谱进行求和比较有趣，所以我要做的是
summation with a spectrum of Pi it's more interesting okay so what I do is I
more interesting okay so what I do is I take the joint but it's factorize like
采取联合，但它像这样分解，然后我推求和
take the joint but it's factorize like this and then I am pushing the summation
this and then I am pushing the summation or X 5 to the right to include only the
或X 5右侧，仅包括取决于X 5的条款，您会注意到
or X 5 to the right to include only the terms that depend on X 5 and you notice
terms that depend on X 5 and you notice I have included X Y given X 3 all right
我将XY赋予X 3包括在内，但x6也赋予了XY的一部分
I have included X Y given X 3 all right but x6 given also it's part of the
but x6 given also it's part of the experience part ok so I have to perform
经验不错，所以我必须对这个学期做一个总结，我们要
experience part ok so I have to perform a summation of this term and we're going
a summation of this term and we're going to call this a new potential we're going
称它为新的潜力，我们将给它起一个名字，我将
to call this a new potential we're going to give it some name and I'm going to
to give it some name and I'm going to call the potential P and I'm going to
叫电位P，我要下标X 5，所以X 5会提醒我
call the potential P and I'm going to put a subscript X 5 so X 5 reminds me
put a subscript X 5 so X 5 reminds me with snow that destination the tree
带着雪，目的地是雄树将要被淘汰的树
with snow that destination the tree which male is going to be eliminated
which male is going to be eliminated okay expiry is to know that I'm doing
好吧，到期是要知道我正在做加法运算以及您在X 5上卖出的时间
okay expiry is to know that I'm doing the summation and when you sell on X 5
the summation and when you sell on X 5 what your master is the potential is
您的主人所具有的潜力将是X 2或X 3的函数，并且
what your master is the potential is going to be a function of X 2 or X 3 and
going to be a function of X 2 or X 3 and X 6 so if you live there the arguments
X 6所以如果你住在那儿，你还没有想到其余的人
X 6 so if you live there the arguments that you haven't thought the rest of you
that you haven't thought the rest of you saw basically whatever your Psalm is
基本上看到了您的诗篇将作为此基础的内容
saw basically whatever your Psalm is going to come as a substrate from this
going to come as a substrate from this potential okay so let's I have say so
潜在的好吧，让我们说一下原始图，它告诉我们
potential okay so let's I have say so business the original graph and it tells
business the original graph and it tells you all the conditional probabilities
你们所有在此定义分布的条件概率
you all the conditional probabilities that define the distributions in this
that define the distributions in this graph you notice this is X 3 given X 1 X
图，您注意到这是给定X 1 X 5和X 3的X 3，但是在这里您必须父代
graph you notice this is X 3 given X 1 X 5 and X 3 but here you have to parent so
5 and X 3 but here you have to parent so this is a table exit given X 2 and X 5
这是给定X 2和X 5此处为三维表的表出口
this is a table exit given X 2 and X 5 the three dimensional table in here
the three dimensional table in here let's you know figure out where the hell
让我们知道弄清楚这张图在哪里说他为什么有这种颜色
let's you know figure out where the hell this graph says why he has this color
this graph says why he has this color when writing the biggest summation X 5
在编写最大和X 5和小的X 5时，请注意
when writing the biggest summation X 5 and the little X 5 but notice what
and the little X 5 but notice what happens now x3 and x6 are coming
现在发生了x3和x6在一种文化中走到一起，这意味着
happens now x3 and x6 are coming together in a culture which means that
together in a culture which means that they're correlated now so I have to do
它们现在是相关的，所以我必须擦拭它们，我的意思是我在这里看到X 3和X
they're correlated now so I have to do wipe to them I mean I see here X 3 and X
wipe to them I mean I see here X 3 and X 6 X 6 they're coming together
6 X 6他们在一起
消灭了小姐，我将不得不基本上连接X 3和X 2 X 6
wipe to them I mean I see here X 3 and X 6 X 6 they're coming together
missus eliminated I'm gonna have to connect basically X 3 and X 2 X 6
在给定人口的背景下讨论任何问题
discussing anything yet in the context of the population here given explain
of the population here given explain this you know when I do a summation this
您知道我进行汇总时，此表将不再存在
this you know when I do a summation this table will not exist anymore
table will not exist anymore this is the table effect sticks given X
这是给定X 2和X 5的桌子效果棒
this is the table effect sticks given X 2 and X 5
2 and X 5 when I integrate X 5 this will be the
当我集成X 5时，这将是X 5组件的总和
when I integrate X 5 this will be the summation of this X 5 component will
summation of this X 5 component will disappear and effectively this
消失，这个三维胶带将有效地变成
disappear and effectively this three-dimensional tape will become
three-dimensional tape will become actually 2 dimension table okay you will
实际上是二维表好吧，您将在这里获得这种潜力
actually 2 dimension table okay you will be getting this potential here that is
be getting this potential here that is declining in terms of this prefix given
在给定极值的前提下，此前缀下降，可以乘以P
declining in terms of this prefix given extreme all right okay multiplied by P
extreme all right okay multiplied by P of X 6 given what is that X 5 and X 2
X 6的给定X 5和X 2的总和X 5是多少，然后我得到这个
of X 6 given what is that X 5 and X 2 summation X 5 and then I get this
因此，通常来说，我要发挥这些潜能的下标是
so generally the subscript I to put on these potentials is the note that you're
these potentials is the note that you're eliminated or you are signing over and
消除或您正在签署，并且多余的hi是以下变量的因变量
eliminated or you are signing over and excess hi are the dependent variables of
excess hi are the dependent variables of come together in the new potential okay
以新的潜力聚在一起，好吧，您以为基本上是
come together in the new potential okay the way that you thought was basically a
the way that you thought was basically a comment in our case because X 2 X 3 and
在我们的案例中发表评论，因为X 2 X 3和X X没问题，所以让我们来看看
comment in our case because X 2 X 3 and X X's all right so let's have seen on
X X's all right so let's have seen on this area notice elimination of
该区域注意消除变量
this area notice elimination of variables
variables elimination are good so this types begin
消除是很好的，所以这种类型完全是这里发生的事情，所以
elimination are good so this types begin out exactly what's going on here so
out exactly what's going on here so let's do the marginalization for what
我们只对theta X 1 X 2感兴趣的东西进行边缘化处理，所以我们
let's do the marginalization for what interested in theta X 1 X 2 only so we
interested in theta X 1 X 2 only so we need to sum on X 3 X 4 X 5 at 6:00
需要在6:00在X 3 X 4 X 5上求和，所以我将做一个求和
need to sum on X 3 X 4 X 5 at 6:00 so I'm going to do the summations one
so I'm going to do the summations one term at the time
从树叶开始一直到现在的学期
term at the time starting from the leaves all the way up
starting from the leaves all the way up to X 3 all right
到X 3，然后我们将看到发生了什么
to X 3 all right and then we will see what happens to the
and then we will see what happens to the down so I leave X 2 X 4 2 X 5 here and I
向下，所以我在这里留下X 2 X 4 2 X 5，并且对X 6求和，所以当我站在
down so I leave X 2 X 4 2 X 5 here and I do a summation on X 6 so when I stand on
do a summation on X 6 so when I stand on its sixth
它的第六名显然是诺维克第六名
its sixth alright obviously the Novik sixth will
alright obviously the Novik sixth will disappear now this is equal to 1 right
现在消失，它等于1对，但让我们忘记它等于1
disappear now this is equal to 1 right but let's forget that it is equal to 1
but let's forget that it is equal to 1 this will give me a potential that I do
这将给我一个我不玩的潜力，因为我订阅了这6个，因为
this will give me a potential that I do not play would subscribe that 6 because
not play would subscribe that 6 because this is the north of the song and the
这是歌曲的北部，可用的选择将过期，所以我是
this is the north of the song and the available selects will expire so I am
available selects will expire so I am giving you so I am going to eliminate
给你，所以我现在要消除X 6并注意那里
giving you so I am going to eliminate now that X 6 all right and notice there
now that X 6 all right and notice there is a dotted line there what is the
是一条虚线，这里的虚线是什么意思
is a dotted line there what is the dotted line implies here
所以在这里通过反向2和5显示了新的潜在线索，那就是
so here have displayed the new potential leads by reverse two and five and that's
leads by reverse two and five and that's what I do in the belly I basically say
我基本上是说我在肚子里做的事35现在已经连接在一起了
what I do in the belly I basically say 35 are now linked together all right
当时需要执行额外的步骤，所以这是一条虚线，但是您现在将看到
an additional step at the time so this is a dotted line but you would see now
is a dotted line but you would see now in the next step I am going to make this
在下一步中，我将使它也只是一个底线，所以它不会
in the next step I am going to make this just a back line as well so it doesn't
just a back line as well so it doesn't you know my first oh here it is this
你知道我的第一个哦，这是这张照片，它将是总结
you know my first oh here it is this picture and it's gonna be summation on
picture and it's gonna be summation on on the so become the destination xx6
在因此成为目的地xx6时，我们得到的潜力取决于X 2
on the so become the destination xx6 we got the potential that depends on X 2
we got the potential that depends on X 2 X 5 and I am going to try and X Prime
X 5，我将尝试使用X Prime，X 5的总和将起作用
X 5 and I am going to try and X Prime and the summation X 5 is gonna operate
and the summation X 5 is gonna operate on this x naught so on this x naught and
在这x零上，在这x零上，新的潜力将有一个下标
on this x naught so on this x naught and the new potential will have a subscript
the new potential will have a subscript X 5 because that's what I saw and what
X 5，因为那是我所看到的，剩下的X 2和X 3以及我在做什么
X 5 because that's what I saw and what is left X 2 and X 3 and what am i doing
is left X 2 and X 3 and what am i doing that
我正在连接X 2和X 3
that I'm connecting X 2 and X 3 all right and
I'm connecting X 2 and X 3 all right and then I would get rid of note 5 leading
那么我会摆脱注释5导致此正常，所以让我们继续
then I would get rid of note 5 leading to this ok all right so let's continue
to this ok all right so let's continue eliminate now if I eliminate there is no
如果我消除了，现在就消除，没有我要担心的依赖项
eliminate now if I eliminate there is no dependencies that I have to worry
dependencies that I have to worry actually this summation comes here to be
实际上，这个总和等于1，所以这个电位等于
actually this summation comes here to be equal to 1 so this potential is equal to
equal to 1 so this potential is equal to 1 so this is eliminated I get a graph
1，这样就消除了，我得到一个像这样的图，然后如果我摆脱了
1 so this is eliminated I get a graph like that and then if I get rid of for
like that and then if I get rid of for node 3 all right so now 3 there were
节点3很好，所以现在3在
node 3 all right so now 3 there were sort of offenses that have generated in
sort of offenses that have generated in in between rights or node 3 I have
在权限或节点3之间，我有一个X 1，但它们有一个
in between rights or node 3 I have expletive an X 1 but they have a
expletive an X 1 but they have a potential to expand that is a function
是X 2和X 3的函数的扩展潜力
potential to expand that is a function of X 2 and X 3
of X 2 and X 3 remember all right the function of X 2
记住X 2和X 3的功能，并且也具有这种潜力
remember all right the function of X 2 and X 3 and and also have this potential
and X 3 and and also have this potential here with the function of X 2 it's equal
在这里X 2的函数等于1，但是在这里我们只保留它
here with the function of X 2 it's equal to 1 but here we just keep it for
to 1 but here we just keep it for decoration purposes why are we
装饰目的我们为什么，所以我们基本上给了X罗恩
decoration purposes why are we and and so we have basically given X Ron
and and so we have basically given X Ron no actually I don't keep it the x 1 x 2
不，实际上我不保留X 2和X 3的x 1 x 2 x 5乘以7 X 3，然后
no actually I don't keep it the x 1 x 2 x 5 of X 2 and X 3 by 7 X 3 and then
x 5 of X 2 and X 3 by 7 X 3 and then what this mask is something depends on
这个蒙版是什么取决于您的x1和x2好的，这是
what this mask is something depends on your x1 and x2 okay and this is
your x1 and x2 okay and this is basically my marginal distribution that
基本上是我要计算的边际分布，所以边际
basically my marginal distribution that I going to compute so the margin
I going to compute so the margin distribution is P of X 1 P of x2 given X
给定X 1和2个电位，其中一个取决于Xtreme，则分布为X 1的P
distribution is P of X 1 P of x2 given X 1 and 2 potentials one depends on Xtreme
1 and 2 potentials one depends on Xtreme Ian one depends on X 1 and X 2 and this
伊恩（Ian）取决于X 1和X 2，而下标又告诉我
Ian one depends on X 1 and X 2 and this again the subscripts telling me the
again the subscripts telling me the notes that the software eliminated as
指出该软件已淘汰，因为它们可以继续进行，因此这使得
notes that the software eliminated as they was proceeding okay so this make
they was proceeding okay so this make any sense
任何感觉都好吧好吧，但是当你
any sense all right okay so right but when you
all right okay so right but when you know whether we started this this dance
知道我们是否开始了这支舞蹈，显然是第一支最高的
know whether we started this this dance here obviously the first the highest
here obviously the first the highest cost in the calculation is the one that
计算中的成本基本上是涉及最高数量的成本
cost in the calculation is the one that involves basically the highest number of
involves basically the highest number of variables in in in this summation so for
求和中的变量，例如，您有两个变量，因此
variables in in in this summation so for example you have two variables so the
example you have two variables so the first of this if each of them can take
首先，如果每个人都可以接受我们的值，将是R平方
first of this if each of them can take our values will be R square right for
our values will be R square right for each 9 FX 3 here 2 is only two variables
每个9 FX 3这里的2只是两个变量，这里我有两个变量，应
each 9 FX 3 here 2 is only two variables and here I have two variables and shall
and here I have two variables and shall have my so this calculation of this
有我的话，这个潜力的计算基本上是最大的
have my so this calculation of this potential will be basically the most
potential will be basically the most expensive in the process and exactly the
过程中很昂贵，而且实际上您可以了解您的本性
expensive in the process and exactly the nature you can actually you know you
nature you can actually you know you will see later on when we talk about
当我们基本上在没有知识的情况下谈论笑声时，将在以后看到
will see later on when we talk about laughs basically without this knowledge
laughs basically without this knowledge determine the maximum click on the
确定我在相应无向图上的最大点击次数
determine the maximum click on the corresponding undirected graph as I do
corresponding undirected graph as I do this elimination process okay so I'm
这个淘汰的过程还可以，所以我很快就可以开始了，但是我
this elimination process okay so I'm gonna start to get shortly okay but I
gonna start to get shortly okay but I just want you to appreciate that maybe
只想让您欣赏，也许您听到的声音中包含三个变量
just want you to appreciate that maybe you hear sound you have three variables
you hear sound you have three variables and you want to sound 1 X 5 for each of
并且您想要为该Revati的每个值听起来1 X 5，所以这
and you want to sound 1 X 5 for each of the values of this Revati much so this
the values of this Revati much so this is for the highest fastest alright so
是为了最快的速度，所以这将定义输出的成本
is for the highest fastest alright so this will define the cost of the output
this will define the cost of the output this is nice
这很好
当您开始执行此消除权利时，您的开始方式有多重要
this will define the cost of the output this is nice
how important is the way you start when you start doing this elimination right
当您开始执行此消除权利时，您的开始方式有多重要
you start doing this elimination right you can stop how many know but if you do
您可以停止了解多少信息，但是如果您只这样做，就可以解决这个小问题
you can stop how many know but if you do only you can take the trivial problem
only you can take the trivial problem and make it very painful so here is a
并使其非常痛苦，所以这是一个问题，假设您拥有所有
and make it very painful so here is a problem let's say if you have all of
problem let's say if you have all of these variables and somebody tells you
这些变量，有人告诉您您要计算让我们看看
these variables and somebody tells you you want to compute let's see let's say
you want to compute let's see let's say you want to I don't know what you want
你想我不知道你想对地球进行什么计算，但是让我们
you want to I don't know what you want to compute of the earth right but let's
to compute of the earth right but let's say we want to eliminate X 1 ok first
说我们想先消除X 1好的，也许您有一些证据，
say we want to eliminate X 1 ok first right maybe you have some evidence and
right maybe you have some evidence and you want to start doing elimination from
您想从X 1开始进行消除，如果消除了试验，
you want to start doing elimination from X 1 if you eliminate the trial what
X 1 if you eliminate the trial what happens I mean I think actually the
发生我的意思是我认为实际上是英里的联合概率分布
happens I mean I think actually the joint probability distribution for miles
joint probability distribution for miles on the graph right if you do militates
在图表右侧，如果您确实先犯了什么，那是怎么回事
on the graph right if you do militates one first what's going on
显示依赖关系现在将在依赖关系的所有各方之间
show the dependencies now will be between party all while it was depend on
between party all while it was depend on everything else good luck you took
其他所有的好运，你采取了某种看起来没有
everything else good luck you took something that sort of was not looking
something that sort of was not looking bad and now we have a graph that it's
不好，现在我们有一个图，它很好地连接了所有正确的数字，
bad and now we have a graph that it's pretty connected all right number and
pretty connected all right number and obviously you have to program this ideas
显然，您必须正确地编写此想法，因为您无法阅读说
obviously you have to program this ideas right so because you cannot read say
right so because you cannot read say what a nice do not move this and do that
不错，不要移动它，而是这样做，因为您知道它只是视觉上的
what a nice do not move this and do that because you know it's just visually you
because you know it's just visually you won't be able to see what's going on so
将无法看到正在发生的事情，所以可以肯定这不是，而是
won't be able to see what's going on so certainly this is really not but look
certainly this is really not but look what happens if I go eliminated sorry X
如果我淘汰了，将会发生什么事抱歉X 3 X 3基本上不引入其他任何东西
what happens if I go eliminated sorry X 3 X 3 basically introduces no additional
3 X 3 basically introduces no additional dependencies because the X 3 comes only
依赖关系，因为X 3仅在给定X 1的情况下出现X 3的概率
dependencies because the X 3 comes only in the probability of X 3 given X 1
in the probability of X 3 given X 1 which is equal to 1 so nothing right ok
等于1，所以没事好不好
which is equal to 1 so nothing right ok nice
好的，所以请记住要对此消除算法进行正式声明
all right so remember to web to this elimination algorithm to formally stated
elimination algorithm to formally stated so let me this is sort of actually for
所以让我说这实际上是出于装饰原因
so let me this is sort of actually for decoration reasons this evidence
decoration reasons this evidence potentials but because it's in the books
潜力，但是因为它在书中，让我们谈谈它，所以您需要说
potentials but because it's in the books let's talk about it so you need to say
let's talk about it so you need to say at least mathematically how we write
至少在数学上，当某些节点时，我们如何写这些总和
at least mathematically how we write this summations when some of the nodes
this summations when some of the nodes are logged out some particular values
被注销了一些特定的值，我们将其表示为X条，因此它是一个
are logged out some particular values and we denote this as X bar so it's an
and we denote this as X bar so it's an old I as a specific value we you know
我将其作为特定值，我们将其称为X条，所以这是
old I as a specific value we you know this as X bar I all right so that's
this as X bar I all right so that's evidence we have so that now basically
我们有证据表明，现在基本上是只能将价值乘以
evidence we have so that now basically is can only take the value by the
is can only take the value by the evidence and cannot change so
证据，不能改变
因此，让我们看看我们如何以各种方式来证明这一证据
is can only take the value by the evidence and cannot change so
so so let's see how are we this evidence is going to come on the in various ways
因此，让我们看看我们如何以各种方式来证明这一证据
is going to come on the in various ways on these estimations so let's say with
根据这些估算值，让我们来说一下我们要计算的内容
on these estimations so let's say with what does it say that we want to compute
what does it say that we want to compute P of x1 given the evidence exists okay
给定证据表明x1的P存在，所以您知道我们观察到了滴答声，我们
P of x1 given the evidence exists okay so you know we observe that ticks and we
so you know we observe that ticks and we won't find what's the condition of x1
给定x2，将无法找到x1的条件，因此显然可以做到这一点
won't find what's the condition of x1 given x2 so obviously to do this
given x2 so obviously to do this calculation we have to find the joint of
计算我们必须找到X 1和X 6的关节，我将其写为关节
calculation we have to find the joint of X 1 and X 6 and I write this as a joint
X 1 and X 6 and I write this as a joint event or X 6 you know this is prescribed
事件或X 6，您知道这是规定的，所以当我猜相同的盘子时，
event or X 6 you know this is prescribed okay so when I guess the same plate by
okay so when I guess the same plate by pushing the summation of seen words in
推动变量2 3 4 5中的所见单词的总和，但请注意
pushing the summation of seen words in the in the variables 2 3 4 5 but notice
the in the variables 2 3 4 5 but notice on this conditional of X 6 given X 2 and
在给定X 2和X 5的X 6的条件下，如果您具有
on this conditional of X 6 given X 2 and X 5 if you have this probability that
X 5 if you have this probability that corresponds basically to accessorize or
基本上对应于配件或三维表的规范
corresponds basically to accessorize or the third dimensional table the precept
the third dimensional table the precept the X 16 take various values that say 0
X 16会接受各种数值，说0和1正确无误，所以如果我给你
the X 16 take various values that say 0 and 1 clear right so if I give you the
and 1 clear right so if I give you the next year next 6 the bar is 1 you're
明年明年6酒吧为1，您将选择其中一个
next year next 6 the bar is 1 you're going to take one of this slice of this
going to take one of this slice of this table all right so this is what this
桌子好吧，这就是这意味着的意思，所以当你说的意思是X 5
table all right so this is what this will imply so when you say mean X 5
will imply so when you say mean X 5 you're going to define a potential 3 X 5
您将要定义一个3 X 5的电位，剩下的山谷将是X 2，
you're going to define a potential 3 X 5 and the valley was left will be X 2 and
and the valley was left will be X 2 and X 3 all right then you have to sum 1 X 4
X 3好，那么您必须求和1 X 4，所以这些是唯一的变量
X 3 all right then you have to sum 1 X 4 so these are the only variables that
so these are the only variables that involve X fourth I'm sorry queries
涉及X第四，我很抱歉现在查询剧院，所以这种潜力
involve X fourth I'm sorry queries theater now actually so this potential
theater now actually so this potential is outside the summation right I left it
在求和权的右边，所以我把它留在右边，因为从特定的
is outside the summation right I left it to the right because from the particular
to the right because from the particular reason so I saw an X for this equal to 1
原因，所以我看到这个等于1的X，那么我必须召集极端
reason so I saw an X for this equal to 1 then I have to summon extreme this
then I have to summon extreme this potential depends on X 3 okay so I have
电位取决于X 3好的，所以我有最差的两个术语的意思，所以它
potential depends on X 3 okay so I have the point of the worst two terms so it
the point of the worst two terms so it will be a new potential 3 X 3 of X 1 and
将是X 1和X 2的新势3 X 3，然后我必须求和1 X 2和
will be a new potential 3 X 3 of X 1 and X 2 and and then I have to sum 1 X 2 and
X 2 and and then I have to sum 1 X 2 and I have the product of two potentials and
我有两个潜力的乘积，并且这是有条件的，我基本上得到
I have the product of two potentials and this conditional and I get basically a
this conditional and I get basically a new potential which is V X 2 and the
新的潜力是VX 2，剩下的唯一变量是
new potential which is V X 2 and the only variable left is
only variable left is Swan and if you so this is the joint
天鹅，如果您愿意，这是联合的权利，如果您需要有条件的话
Swan and if you so this is the joint alright and if you want the conditional
alright and if you want the conditional given the evidence x6 bar is basically
给定证据x6条基本上是最终结果
given the evidence x6 bar is basically this is the final result
this is the final result okay so so this is sort of a way one of
好的，所以这是一种通过以下方式计算证据的方式之一
okay so so this is sort of a way one of the ways to calculate the evidence by
the ways to calculate the evidence by taking slices of this table okay
把这张桌子切成薄片好吧，您不需要这个唯一的方法
taking slices of this table okay you don't need this the only way that
you don't need this the only way that you can account for evidence is using
您可以说明证据是使用圆圈Delta函数好吗，所以这句话
you can account for evidence is using circle Delta function okay so the adage
circle Delta function okay so the adage sort of power to reveal a good thing you
可以通过这种方式揭示您曾经编程过的美好事物的力量，但可以说
sort of power to reveal a good thing you ever program it this way but let's say
ever program it this way but let's say rather some node if you give it the
而不是某个节点，如果您赋予它值，那么您正在尝试的是
rather some node if you give it the value so what you do is you are trying
value so what you do is you are trying to that node a potential that you can
到那个节点，您可以证明其潜力的潜力，并且该潜力是
to that node a potential that you can evidence potential and that potential is
evidence potential and that potential is a function do the observable of a
一个功能可以观察到从中选择切片
a function do the observable of a selection of the slice from that
selection of the slice from that conditional distribution without doing
有条件的分布而没有进行显式显示
conditional distribution without doing it sort of explicit to show for example
it sort of explicit to show for example if you want to write the probability
如果您想写下几率，可以说我们知道
if you want to write the probability let's say of let's say we have you know
let's say of let's say we have you know this probability of x given X 2 and X 5
给定X 2和X 5的x的概率，所以使用此证据
this probability of x given X 2 and X 5 all right so using this evidence
all right so using this evidence potential for now the 6 because the node
因为节点X 6紧贴此值，所以现在有6的潜力，您可以使用此值
potential for now the 6 because the node X 6 is clung to this value you use this
X 6 is clung to this value you use this potential and you say when someone at 6
潜力，你说当某人在6时，显然4 X 6的总和
potential and you say when someone at 6 and obviously this summation 4 X 6 will
and obviously this summation 4 X 6 will give you an exit bar right because
给您一个退出栏的权利，因为这是6可以取的唯一值
give you an exit bar right because that's the only value of 6 can take
that's the only value of 6 can take usually programming like this but you
通常像这样编程，但是您知道有点想用它编写
usually programming like this but you know sort of want to write it in in
know sort of want to write it in in in in a generic way mathematical you can
用数学的通用方式，您可以说提供商已经给了
in in a generic way mathematical you can say the providers have given have
say the providers have given have married assigning an evidence potential
已婚人士除具备以下条件外，还分配了潜在的证据
married assigning an evidence potential in addition to the condition of
in addition to the condition of distributions so when you write the
分布，因此当您编写分布时，图形的焦点便是
distributions so when you write the distribution the focus of the graph you
distribution the focus of the graph you also multiplied with the saboteurs
也基本上从其他方面乘以破坏者的潜能
also multiplied with the saboteurs potentials from the rest basically in
potentials from the rest basically in the elimination algorithm is exactly is
消除算法恰好是以前的，它们基本上是我
the elimination algorithm is exactly is before and they're basically I
before and they're basically I generalized this with disturb this
泛化了这一点，扰乱了这种保护
generalized this with disturb this protection
protection all right so change the algorithm the
好的，所以改变算法，消除算法，并指示
all right so change the algorithm the elimination algorithm and directed
elimination algorithm and directed graphs so you have a graph G with
图，所以你有一个图G，其中T确实存在，让我看看
graphs so you have a graph G with evidence T actually exists let me see
证据是证据节点也是计划节点的工作
so is the evidence yes the evidence nodes an effort of the planning node
nodes an effort of the planning node okay so using Jordans notation here so
好的，所以在这里使用Jordans表示法，所以您需要做的是
okay so using Jordans notation here so so what you need to do is you need to
so what you need to do is you need to initialize the graph okay basically yeah
初始化图表好吧，基本上是好的，是要了解潜力
initialize the graph okay basically yeah the good is to understand the potentials
the good is to understand the potentials that you have if you need to introduce
如果需要引入证据，则说明节点已规定
that you have if you need to introduce the evidence what nodes have prescribed
the evidence what nodes have prescribed values and sort of you know the
值和您了解我们讨论过的功能，如果
values and sort of you know the functions that we discussed it then if
functions that we discussed it then if you need to update the graph given the
您需要根据证据来更新图表，因此基本上我会假设
you need to update the graph given the evidence so basically I will assume that
evidence so basically I will assume that see the next slide this is where this
看到下一张幻灯片，这是消除算法要去的地方
see the next slide this is where this elimination algorithm is going to to
elimination algorithm is going to to happen and then effectively you have to
发生，然后有效地您必须将其标准化到该位置，让我们来看看
happen and then effectively you have to normalize to this location let's see the
normalize to this location let's see the details of what they saw what it was do
他们看到的东西的详细信息，然后我们将一无所获
details of what they saw what it was do and then we'll come back to it nothing
and then we'll come back to it nothing on the top so let's have initialization
在顶部，所以让我们进行初始化（如果您选择），我认为这非常
on the top so let's have initialization if you choose and I think this is very
if you choose and I think this is very important in ordering charts for the
重要的是在查询节点的排序图表中出现的最后一个
important in ordering charts for the query nodes are appearing the last
好吧，所以您基本上是淘汰订单，我们正在商店中
okay so you an elimination ordering basically Department we were doing store
basically Department we were doing store let's say probability of X 1 given the
假设给定证据正确时X 1的概率，因此您需要20个音符
let's say probability of X 1 given the evidence right so you want the 20 notes
evidence right so you want the 20 notes to appear the last basically in the in
以消除顺序和
to appear the last basically in the in the elimination order and in the
the elimination order and in the initialization for its note
对其注的初始化Yuma请放置条件
initialization for its note Yuma please place the conditional
Yuma please place the conditional probability in the activation potentials
激活电位的可能性，因此您将保留重要的
probability in the activation potentials so you're gonna keep significant list of
so you're gonna keep significant list of the kind all the positions in the
善于解决问题中的所有职位以及最有可能发动的工作
the kind all the positions in the problem and best potentials to start
problem and best potentials to start would be this elimination so this is
就是这种淘汰，所以这就是您的出发点，显然您
would be this elimination so this is what you start with and obviously you
what you start with and obviously you need to have an active list because
需要有一个活动列表，因为稍后您将在活动列表中
need to have an active list because later on in the active list you are
later on in the active list you are going to help them to reduce these
当我们消除时，将帮助他们减少这些潜力
going to help them to reduce these potentials when we do elimination
potentials when we do elimination variables so this active list will keep
变量，因此此活动列表将跟踪其中的一种潜力
variables so this active list will keep track of one of the potentials that
track of one of the potentials that define the factorization of your joint
在地面上定义您的关节的分解，好吧，我们初始化并
define the factorization of your joint in the ground okay so we initialize and
in the ground okay so we initialize and you plate this active list where you put
您将这个活动列表放在所有这些条件分布的位置
you plate this active list where you put all this conditional distributions you
all this conditional distributions you have to put the elements effectively for
必须在每个证据中有效地为每个节点放置元素
have to put the elements effectively for every node in the evidence you have to
every node in the evidence you have to place this evidence potential all right
放置这个证据潜力没事，您会注意到它说购买了
place this evidence potential all right okay and you notice it says purchase the
okay and you notice it says purchase the evidence potential on the active list so
在活动清单上有潜在的证据，所以您有很多这样的选择
evidence potential on the active list so you have got a great sort of these
you have got a great sort of these sample functions this type of the
样本功能可以处理这种类型的总体，因为当您处于
sample functions this type of the population because when you're in the
population because when you're in the factorization you're also going to
因式分解，您还将乘以乘以6的事实
factorization you're also going to multiply and say let's say well fact six
multiply and say let's say well fact six for mac six bar because x6 cannot take
对于Mac的六杠，因为x6不能在接下来的六杠处取其他任何值
for mac six bar because x6 cannot take any other value by the next six bar okay
any other value by the next six bar okay so this will be part of the alright so
所以这将是好的一部分，这就是通过的证据
so this will be part of the alright so this is what the evident passed this is
this is what the evident passed this is what the initialization does setting is
初始化设置的是活动列表中的电位，以及
what the initialization does setting is potentials from the active list and
potentials from the active list and let's say be a beta so you both need the
假设您是测试版，那么你们俩都需要消除顺序中的知识
let's say be a beta so you both need the knowledge in the elimination order you
knowledge in the elimination order you think the potentials in the active list
认为包含知识的活动列表中的潜力
think the potentials in the active list that contains the knowledge
that contains the knowledge and then go remove us from the after
然后将我们从XI中删除，然后
and then go remove us from the after this is going to be summation X I and
this is going to be summation X I and you are going to come up with a new
您将提出一个新的XI的潜在P，然后您得到了
you are going to come up with a new potential P of X I and then you have got
potential P of X I and then you have got a place that we are assigned the octave
一个分配了八度音阶的地方，其他所有东西都会消失
a place that we are assigned the octave later everything else will disappear
later everything else will disappear from the actively
从积极
这不是很好的信息，真的不再需要它们了，所以如果
later everything else will disappear from the actively
this is not good information is really didn't need them anymore alright so if
这不是很好的信息，真的不再需要它们了，所以如果
didn't need them anymore alright so if you are going to sum over this service
您将总结这项服务的潜在潜力
you are going to sum over this service the potentials basically that involved
the potentials basically that involved three they have no big sigh all right so
三个他们没什么好感叹的，所以你召唤十一，你摆脱了那些
three they have no big sigh all right so you summon X I and you get rid of those
you summon X I and you get rid of those products and you stop see those
产品，然后您停止查看含f3氧化物​​的电位，好吧，等等
products and you stop see those potentials with f3 oxide okay and so
potentials with f3 oxide okay and so that's the update and then of course
那是更新，然后当然当您完成并达到
that's the update and then of course when you finish and you have reached
when you finish and you have reached your query notes what you need to do is
您的查询记录了您需要做的是您需要的，这些都是潜在的
your query notes what you need to do is you need these are the the potentials
you need these are the the potentials that only refer to the query - except
只引用查询-除非必须对所有这些进行规范化
that only refer to the query - except obviously have to normalize those all
obviously have to normalize those all right and then get one okay so you are
正确，然后就可以了，这样您就可以进行计算了
right and then get one okay so you are going that way you have going to compute
going that way you have going to compute the conditional distribution of x given
给定X我们有正确的x的条件分布，但让我尝试
the conditional distribution of x given X we have right but let me try to
X we have right but let me try to rapidly see if we can introduce here
快速查看我们是否可以在这里介绍图形化处理的情况
rapidly see if we can introduce here what's going on with graphically want to
what's going on with graphically want to do this process so we're going again at
做这个过程，所以我们要再次进行这个估算，以便提出
do this process so we're going again at this estimation all right so to come up
this estimation all right so to come up with potential we have this product that
有潜力的我们拥有包含所有XI且包含在其中的XI的产品
with potential we have this product that contains X I all right and contained in
contains X I all right and contained in this potentials would know that ty
这种潜能会知道你没事，而这些知识会引起注意
this potentials would know that ty all right and this knowledge the notes
all right and this knowledge the notes that are actually related with what I
实际上与图中的消除集团有关
that are actually related with what I call the elimination clique in the graph
call the elimination clique in the graph so identification of a set of nodes
因此，确定一组节点的权利可以断开它的连接，例如
so identification of a set of nodes right to disconnect it alright so as the
right to disconnect it alright so as the elimination process happens I have
消除过程发生了，我整合了三个创意
elimination process happens I have creative three notes I integrate over
creative three notes I integrate over one node and then I'm elected with let's
一个节点，然后当我选出两个节点时，除了窍门
one node and then I'm elected with let's say two nodes all right but the trick
say two nodes all right but the trick that I'm eliminating one node has three
我要消除一个节点有三个注意事项，即消除集团和
that I'm eliminating one node has three notes that's the elimination clique and
notes that's the elimination clique and the maximum of this cliques is going to
这种派系的最大值将定义算法的复杂性
the maximum of this cliques is going to define the complexity of the algorithm
所以你可以看看这个吗，你认识不同的人并思考
so
so can you look at this you know different people for graphs and think
所以你可以看看这个吗，你认识不同的人并思考
different people for graphs and think elimination I would have been proceeding
消灭我本来会一直在研究一种方法，然后告诉我
elimination I would have been proceeding with a method by the time and tell me
with a method by the time and tell me which one do you think is going to be
您认为哪一个在计算上会更加复杂
which one do you think is going to be more complicated computationally
more complicated computationally speaking do you look at the definitions
说的话，您会看一下定义，但是如果您正在学习的话，请看一下这个定义
speaking do you look at the definitions but look at this if you're studying I
but look at this if you're studying I mean anything
一次意味着一个节点的任何意思，那么您必须
mean anything one node at a time and then you have to
one node at a time and then you have to do summation over the affiliated no to
对没有巧克力奶昔进行关联求和
do summation over the affiliated no to that no chocolate shake
that no chocolate shake it's really my neighbors know how many
真的，我的邻居知道电位中有多少个节点与
it's really my neighbors know how many nodes in the potentials are related to
nodes in the potentials are related to this node how many
这个节点多少
所以从这里开始，如果你在那里，你就会知道他们是流行音乐的联合者
nodes in the potentials are related to this node how many
so from here if you are there the you know they're the joint right the pop
所以从这里开始，如果你在那里，你就会知道他们是流行音乐的联合者
know they're the joint right the pop your eyes and you want to eliminate this
你的眼睛，你想消除这一点，你在那张纸条上看到了多少
your eyes and you want to eliminate this and you saw over that note how many in
and you saw over that note how many in the potential that is that you're going
的潜力是，您将要做多少个或
the potential that is that you're going to be doing the some how many or the
to be doing the some how many or the body will start involved
身体将开始介入
我的名字是粉红色，好吧，你要拥有什么
to be doing the some how many or the body will start involved
my name's pinky all right what are you gonna have you're gonna have the
我的名字是粉红色，好吧，你要拥有什么
gonna have you're gonna have the probability of this given that and the
给定那个的概率和给定那么多的概率
probability of this given that and the probability of that given that so many
probability of that given that so many coming in knowledge involve this how
知识的介入涉及到多少次，我们有多少次
coming in knowledge involve this how many times we have how many how many
这实际上有25次让我们说出现问题的次数，所以如果您计算一下
how many times this actually 25 let's say comes problem so so if you calculate
say comes problem so so if you calculate right here we define the period as the
在这里，我们将时期定义为医院献祭的最小规模
right here we define the period as the minimum size of a hospital immolations
minimum size of a hospital immolations of the rats monthly created during golf
高尔夫淘汰期间每月产生的老鼠数-1，因此单击此处全部
of the rats monthly created during golf elimination - 1 so the click here is all
elimination - 1 so the click here is all right because I reversed in Iran and we
对，因为我在伊朗逆转了，我们把减号1放了，因为这是一个
right because I reversed in Iran and we put the minus 1 because this is a
put the minus 1 because this is a twisting action we want to have this
扭曲动作，我们希望这个变量等于森林等于1 all
twisting action we want to have this variable that forest is equal to 1 all
variable that forest is equal to 1 all right
在这种情况下，基本上这是唯一的
right in this case basically this is the only
in this case basically this is the only potential you know that you will work
您知道自己将与之合作的潜力，这就是点击器的点击
potential you know that you will work with so this is the click the clickers
with so this is the click the clickers is of size Q minus 1 the thing which we
大小为Q减去1我们定义为等于1的事物
is of size Q minus 1 the thing which we defined to be equal to 1
所以你要如何消除这种情况
so how do you want to eliminate this all right
right what is going on well actually let's
进行中的事情实际上让我们掌握了一些比较有成就的东西
what is going on well actually let's take something more accomplished you
take something more accomplished you know take something more complicated
知道做些更复杂的事在这里做些事你知道你知道
know take something more complicated take something here you know you know
take something here you know you know how many you know how many things we
有多少你知道我们需要消除多少东西，所以如果你尝试
how many you know how many things we need to eliminate so if you try to
need to eliminate so if you try to eliminate this while we have to do
消除这一点，而我们必须按顺序执行一些操作，让我们看看哪个
eliminate this while we have to do something in sequence so let's see which
something in sequence so let's see which will eliminate
将消除
我的意思是认为这件事上下起伏不定，所以这是一个
something in sequence so let's see which will eliminate
I mean consider that this thing goes up and downs right so it is a
我的意思是认为这件事上下起伏不定，所以这是一个
and downs right so it is a two-dimensional graph looking like that
看起来像这样的二维图，没关系，让我们集中精力
two-dimensional graph looking like that so it doesn't matter let's concentrate
so it doesn't matter let's concentrate on this on this node and let's say we
在这个节点上，假设我们已经消除了这个，那么多少
on this on this node and let's say we have eliminated this so how many how
have eliminated this so how many how many potentials how many vegetables
有很多潜力，有多少蔬菜可以消灭，什么是消灭
many potentials how many vegetables where eliminate what is the elimination
where eliminate what is the elimination click where the summation is going to
单击求和将在何处进行操作将涉及多少个节点
click where the summation is going to operate how many nodes will involve
operate how many nodes will involve let's say this now we assume this
假设现在假设我们已经将其消除了
let's say this now we assume this already we eliminate it to the right how
already we eliminate it to the right how many how many 3 so 3 minus 1 so the 3
3 3 3减1所以3的宽度是2
many how many 3 so 3 minus 1 so the 3 width is 2 and the chatter a more
width is 2 and the chatter a more complicated case
复杂的案件，所以很明显，如果每个人
complicated case so obviously the nation's if everybody
so obviously the nation's if everybody both can take K values the cost of every
两者都可以取K值，每个通知的成本k2 w加1不能使用3
both can take K values the cost of every notice k2 w plus 1 could not use the 3
notice k2 w plus 1 could not use the 3 wait and then times V this gives you the
等待，然后乘以V，如果没有，则为您提供计算顺序
wait and then times V this gives you the order of the calculation if you didn't
order of the calculation if you didn't give elimination I would basically the
给消除，我基本上成本将是K等于D的幂
give elimination I would basically the cost would be K to the power D all right
cost would be K to the power D all right D is the total number of nodes so
D是节点的总数，因此很明显，它在V中是线性的，所以它是V
D is the total number of nodes so obviously this is linear in V so it's V
obviously this is linear in V so it's V times K 2w plus 1
乘以K 2w加1等等很多东西
times K 2w plus 1 and lots of kinds of things so many
and lots of kinds of things so many lectures we think with the plus 1
我们认为加号1的讲座，因为您知道12岁大了1
lectures we think with the plus 1 because you know 12 years big the 1
because you know 12 years big the 1 doesn't make much difference but this is
并没有太大的区别，但这是正确的路线列表的一种
doesn't make much difference but this is the sort of the correct route list okay
因此，最好的是在无向图的背景下，我提到了我们
so the best and in the context of undirected graphs okay I mentioned we
undirected graphs okay I mentioned we are gonna be here in the Big Show you
将会出现在大秀中，您可以统一有向和无向
are gonna be here in the Big Show you can unify the directed and undirected
can unify the directed and undirected graphs with the addition of a little bit
有一点点的图形，因为我还没有
graphs with the addition of a little bit ahead of ourselves because I haven't
ahead of ourselves because I haven't discussed the factorization of the Joint
讨论了无向图上联合分布的因式分解，但是
discussed the factorization of the Joint Distribution over undirected graphs but
Distribution over undirected graphs but let me just state it alright so then
我只说一声好吧，那么我们在这里会很困难，我们
let me just state it alright so then we're gonna be difficult here and we
we're gonna be difficult here and we will come back to this in details in the
将会在图表中详细介绍这一点，请记住，我们拥有
will come back to this in details in the graphs you know the remember we have the
graphs you know the remember we have the probability of fabric now attacks
现在，从您的角度分析，面料的概率会攻击发展
probability of fabric now attacks developments in analyzed in terms of you
developments in analyzed in terms of you know is X 1 X 2 X 5 X 3 it lik know why
知道是X 1 X 2 X 5 X 3，它知道为什么是因为未连接X 1和X 5
know is X 1 X 2 X 5 X 3 it lik know why because X 1 and X 5 are not connected
because X 1 and X 5 are not connected because X 2 X they are not connected so
因为X 2 X在这里连接起来不那么容易，所以您有足够的空间
because X 2 X they are not connected so easily here that you have a sufficient
easily here that you have a sufficient undirected graph you have this clique we
无向图，你有这个集团，我们有这个集团，你有这个集团
undirected graph you have this clique we have this clique you have this clique
have this clique you have this clique and then you have it later of 3 and then
然后您拥有3的后期，然后您拥有2的集团，因此每个
and then you have it later of 3 and then you have a clique of 2 so each of these
you have a clique of 2 so each of these cliques comes with the potential note
势力附带潜在的注意事项
cliques comes with the potential note the distribution just the potential of
the distribution just the potential of those functions that sort of explains
那些解释良好变量的函数是相关的
those functions that sort of explains well standing variables are correlated
well standing variables are correlated involved late right but they're you know
涉及迟到的权利，但他们是您知道的分布其潜力的您所知道的
involved late right but they're you know distributions their potentials you know
distributions their potentials you know if you elimination on undirected graphs
如果您消除无向图，它们实际上将是一个
if you elimination on undirected graphs they will be actually literally is a
they will be actually literally is a typical form of the algorithm for
有向图算法的典型形式，但是很荒谬
typical form of the algorithm for directed graphs but it's ridiculous
directed graphs but it's ridiculous complicated because there is no errors
因为没有错误或类似的东西所以很复杂，所以当我有
complicated because there is no errors or anything like that so when I have
or anything like that so when I have been in this Bluff I took the joint
曾经在这个虚张声势中，我参加了联合发行，我喜欢它
been in this Bluff I took the joint distribution I loved it in terms of
distribution I loved it in terms of potential over rocks more clicks as I
就像我刚刚在这里所说的那样，我可以喘不过气来
potential over rocks more clicks as I just called here alright I panting the
just called here alright I panting the evidence as you see in here okay and
您在这里看到的证据还可以，然后找到我的求和点
evidence as you see in here okay and then to find this joint I the summations
就像我们用很少的图所做的一样，旋转实际上是
and exactly as we did with very few graphs the rotation is practically
graphs the rotation is practically identical
完全相同，这是您看到的东西
identical this is thing that you see that is
this is thing that you see that is different here from what we did with
这与我们编写有向图时所做的不同
different here from what we did with directed graphs when you write this
directed graphs when you write this joint probabilities in terms of these
在这些潜力方面的联合概率，此优化无法实现
joint probabilities in terms of these potentials this optimization does not
potentials this optimization does not give you normalize distribution so the
给您归一化分布，所以归一化因子基本上是
give you normalize distribution so the normalization factor basically there is
normalization factor basically there is not no but eventually when you give me
不是，但是最终当你给我很多血的时候，你就可以
not no but eventually when you give me lots of blood alright then you can fill
lots of blood alright then you can fill this joint and you want this conditional
这个关节，您想要这个条件，那么您实际上并不需要Z，因为一旦您
this joint and you want this conditional you don't really need Z because once you
you don't really need Z because once you get this potential this is what you
发挥这种潜力，这就是您所相信的
get this potential this is what you believe this
believe this this conditional distribution and it is
这种有条件的分布，这就是我们要做的，这样橇就可以
this conditional distribution and it is what we're gonna do is so the skids can
what we're gonna do is so the skids can invade the room where the stress in
入侵压力在起作用的房间，然后我们将合并
invade the room where the stress in action and then we are going to merge
action and then we are going to merge the two algorithms and give you sort of
两种算法，并为您提供了一种基于图论的方法
the two algorithms and give you sort of a graph theoretic approach with
a graph theoretic approach with elimination of cliques but we'll do the
消除集团，但我们会消除它，所以您实际上并不会
elimination of cliques but we'll do the elimination of it so you don't really
elimination of it so you don't really have to say division of variables but
不得不说变量的除法，但基本上你一直在消除
have to say division of variables but basically you've been at eliminating
basically you've been at eliminating nodes one at the same time deprived of
一个节点同时被剥夺了点击次数，并且也消除了
nodes one at the same time deprived of the clicks for this and also eliminated
the clicks for this and also eliminated there will be some marriage with some
将会发生一些婚姻，并在某些组织过程中发生
there will be some marriage with some organization process happening in the
organization process happening in the process and some other weird things but
过程和其他一些奇怪的事情，但它们都是理论方法
process and some other weird things but they will all be theoretical approaches
they will all be theoretical approaches so will be operations on the graph not
所以图表上的运算将不再存在于分布中了
so will be operations on the graph not in the distribution anymore okay
in the distribution anymore okay so actually so you can do it you can be
所以实际上，所以你可以做到，你可以领先我，我会说记住你
so actually so you can do it you can be ahead of me and I will say remember you
ahead of me and I will say remember you sometime in the very near future
在不久的将来的某个时间还可以，所以对于前者的任何情况
sometime in the very near future okay so for any conditions in the former
okay so for any conditions in the former Rubick
鲁比克